<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version='4'>
	<sets>
		<set>
			<name>BOO3</name>
			<longname>Strata Games BOO Cube 2026</longname>
			<settype>Custom</settype>
			<releasedate>2026-05-02</releasedate>
		</set>
	</sets>
	<cards>
		<card>
			<name>Lethal Inheritance</name>
			<text>Hidden adversary (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose an opponent.)
If the chosen opponent would lose the game, you may turn this conspiracy face up and reveal the chosen opponent, then conjure a duplicate of up to three cards from among nonland permanents they control and nonland cards in their graveyard into your hand. Spells conjured this way perpetually gain &quot;You may spend mana as though it were mana of any color to cast this spell.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/0.png" num="11">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Enlightened by Nyx</name>
			<text>Creatures you control get +1/+1 for each of their colors.
At the beginning of combat on your turn, choose a color at random that hasn&apos;t been chosen this way. Creatures you control become the chosen color in addition to their other colors, then if there are five or more colors among nontoken creatures you control, create a 0/0 Archon enchantment creature token with flying and haste that&apos;s all colors.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/1.png" num="35">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>4W</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kitewing Companion</name>
			<text>Flying, first strike
Whenever this creature attacks a player, if it was saddled this turn, reveal cards from the top of your library until you reveal a creature card with lesser power than the total power of creatures that saddled this creature this turn. Put that creature card onto the battlefield tapped and attacking that player, then put the rest of the cards revealed this way onto the bottom of your library in a random order.
Saddle 1 (Tap any number of other creatures you control with total power 1 or more: This Mount becomes saddled until end of turn. Saddle only as a sorcery.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/2.png" num="43">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Bird Ally Mount</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Selfish Sire</name>
			<text>Whenever a nontoken creature an opponent controls enters, they may put a vow counter on that creature. If they don&apos;t, you create a tapped Treasure token.
Creatures with vow counters on them can&apos;t attack you or planeswalkers you control unless their controller pays {2} for each of those creatures that&apos;s attacking you or a planeswalker you control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/3.png" num="55">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Noble</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shirefield Shepherd // Rally the Ranch</name>
			<text>At the beginning of combat on your turn, put a +1/+1 counter on each livestock you control. (Birds, Boars, Eggs, Fish, Goats, Horses, Llamas, Oxen, Rabbits, and Sheep are livestock.) 

---

Choose up to X. (You may only choose each mode once.)
• Create three 1/1 white Sheep creature tokens.
• Create two 2/1 red Ox creature tokens.
• Create two 1/2 green Boar creature tokens.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/4.png" num="57">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Peasant // Sorcery — Adventure</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W // XXW</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gatekeep</name>
			<text>Will of the Council — Choose target spell. Starting with you, each player other than that spell&apos;s controller votes for misdirection or denial. If misdirection gets more votes, return that spell to its owner&apos;s hand, then draw a card. If denial got more votes or the vote is tied, counter that spell.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/5.png" num="80">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>UU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>An Ode to Dusk</name>
			<text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter.)
Each opponent draws a card. You draw a card for each opponent who drew a card this way.
Noncreature spells you cast this turn cost {U}{U} (or {2}) less to cast.
Exile this Saga, then return it to the battlefield transformed under your control.
Each opponent creates a 1/1 white Soldier creature token. You 1/1 white Soldier creature token for each opponent who created a token this way.
Creatures you control get +1/+1, vigilance, and lifelink until end of turn.
---
(Back): A Ballad to Dawn</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/6_front.png" num="91a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Saga</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3U</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">A Ballad to Dawn</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>A Ballad to Dawn</name>
			<text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter.)
---
(Front): An Ode to Dusk</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/6_back.png" num="91b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Saga</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">An Ode to Dusk</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Scheming Spectre</name>
			<text>Shadow (This creature can block or be blocked by only creatures with shadow.)
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, if there is no monarch, that player becomes the monarch.
Whenever an opponent draws their second card during each of their turns, this creature connives. (Draw a card, then discard a card. If you discarded a nonland card, put a +1/+1 counter on that creature.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/7.png" num="97">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spirit Rogue Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Yunne, the Starblessed</name>
			<text>Vigilance, haste
Yunne can&apos;t be blocked or sacrificed.
At the beginning of each opponent&apos;s first main phase, that player gains control of Yunne until end of turn. Goad it.
If Yunne would deal combat damage to an opponent, prevent that damage and exile that many cards from the top of that player&apos;s library. Yunne&apos;s owner may cast nonland cards exiled this way for as long as they remain exiled, and they may put five other cards exiled with Yunne into their owners&apos; graveyard rather than pay that spell&apos;s mana cost.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/8.png" num="113">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Alien Whale God</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Keeper of the Silent Citadel</name>
			<text>Flying, lifelink
At the beginning of your end step, choose target opponent. Return a creature card at random from the chosen player&apos;s graveyard to the battlefield under your control with a finality counter on it. You and its owner each lose life equal to its power.
{2}{B}, Sacrifice another creature: The sacrificed creature&apos;s owner mills cards equal to its power. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/9.png" num="142">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dragon Horror Knight</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>The Trial of the Heart</name>
			<text>Flash
At the beginning of each end step, you draw a card and you lose 1 life.
You don&apos;t lose the game for having less than 0 life. (You can still lose the game for having exactly 0 life.)
As long as you have less than 0 life, if you would lose life, you gain that much life instead. (Damage causes loss of life.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/10.png" num="158">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>4BB</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gaslight</name>
			<text>Gaslight deals 3 damage to any target. You may goad a creature dealt damage this way. Until your next turn, you and permanents you control can&apos;t be the target of spells or abilities controlled by an opponent dealt damage this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/11.png" num="179">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sword of Storm and Sunder</name>
			<text>Whenever equipped creature attacks, add {E}{E} (two energy counters).
Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage to a player, you may pay an amount of {E} equal to the damage dealt and sacrifice this artifact. If you do, that creature deals that much damage to each creature and planeswalker that player controls. It deals half that much damage, rounded up, to each other opponent and each creature and planeswalker they control.
Equip {3}</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/12.png" num="203">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Equipment</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Taleless Traitor</name>
			<text>Whenever this creature attacks an opponent, each other creature attacking that opponent gets +1/+0 until end of turn. 
{2}{BR}{BR}: Return this creature from your graveyard to the battlefield under target opponent&apos;s control with a finality counter on it. It&apos;s a black Skeleton with menace, haste, and decayed in addition to its other types and abilities. Goad up to three creatures that player controls. (A decayed creature can&apos;t block. When it attacks, sacrifice it at end of combat.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/13.png" num="204">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Pirate</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cull-Beast Channeler</name>
			<text>{T}: Add one mana of any color. Spend this mana only to cast non-Human creature spells.
{1}{G}, {T}, Sacrifice this creature: Choose target creature you control, then choose one. If the chosen creature is a Beast, Dinosaur, or Elemental, choose any number instead.
• The chosen creature gets +2/+0 and trample until end of turn.
• The chosen creature deals damage equal to its power to another creature.
• Destroy an artifact or enchantment with mana value less than the chosen creature&apos;s power.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/14.png" num="223">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Shaman</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Embrace the Wilds</name>
			<text>Put three +1/+1 counters on target creature you control. Starting with the player to your left, each player chooses a keyword that hasn&apos;t been chosen from among flying, first strike, deathtouch, hexproof, indestructible, lifelink, menace, trample and vigilance. For each keyword chosen this way, put a counter of that kind on that creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/15.png" num="230">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2GG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Reyjin, Prismatic Philosopher</name>
			<text>Flying
Whenever you activate an ability of a permanent you control, if it isn&apos;t a mana ability, you may copy that ability. If you do, that permanent loses that ability (indefinitely). You may choose new targets for the copy.
{4}: Add {W}{U}{B}{R}{G}. Spend this mana only to activate abilities of other permanents you control. Activate only as a sorcery and only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/16.png" num="245">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Dragon Druid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bringer of Evolution</name>
			<text>Each non-Human creature card in your hand has mutate. The mutate cost is equal to that creature&apos;s mana cost reduced by {2}. (If you cast that spell for its mutate cost, put it over or under target non-Human creature you own. They mutate into the creature on top plus all abilities from under it.)
Whenever a creature you control mutates, trigger each of its enters abilities.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/17.png" num="259">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Scientist</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hazoret, the God-Survivor</name>
			<text>Vigilance, trample, indestructible
At the beginning of combat on your turn, choose a player with the fewest cards in hand or tied for the fewest, they become the monarch.
Hazoret can&apos;t attack or block unless you&apos;re the monarch.
{2}, Discard a card: Exile the top two cards of your library, You may play those cards this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/18.png" num="270">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — God</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2RW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gadgeteer Auctioneer</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
After you draft a nonland card, you may remove it from the draft face down. (Those cards aren&apos;t in your card pool.)
At the beginning of your end step, you may reveal a card at random from among cards you removed from the draft with cards named Gadgeteer Auctioneer. Each player may bid life. You start the bidding with a bid of any number. In turn order, each player may top the high bid. The bidding ends if the high bid stands. The high bidder loses life equal to the high bid and casts the revealed spell without paying its mana cost. If you were not the high bidder, you gain life equal to the high bid and create that many treasure tokens.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/19.png" num="314">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct Citizen</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Symbiotic Starship</name>
			<text>Station (Tap another creature you control: Put charge counters equal to its power on this Spacecraft. Station only as a sorcery.)
Whenever this artifact or equipped creature attacks, it gets +2/+2 and gains flying until end of turn. Draw two cards, then discard a card.
Reconfigure—Remove two charge counters from this artifact. (Attach to target creature you control; or unattach from a creature. Reconfigure only as a sorcery. While attached, this isn&apos;t a creature.)
Remove four charge counters from this artifact: This artifact becomes a creature in addition to its other types until end of turn. Activate only as a sorcery and only if this artifact isn&apos;t attached to another creature. [4/4]</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/20.png" num="324">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Equipment Spacecraft Vehicle</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Glacial Awakening</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
Before drawing your opening hand, choose a basic land type.
Lands you control of the chosen type are snow in addition to their their types.
Snowfall — Whenever you cast a snow spell or a snow land you control enters, surveil 1.
{4}{S}{S}: Target snow land becomes a 6/6 Dinosaur creature with trample and haste. It&apos;s still a land.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/21.png" num="7">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Adrift in the Aether</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, exile target creature.
When this enchantment leaves the battlefield, return the exiled creature to the battlefield under its owner&apos;s control.
Disturb {4}{W}{W} (You may cast this card from your graveyard transformed for its disturb cost.)
---
(Back): Magnanimity</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/22_front.png" num="22a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1WW</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Magnanimity</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magnanimity</name>
			<text>Ward {2} (Whenever this permanent becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {2}.)
At the beginning of your end step, you may choose one —
• You and target opponent each draw a card.
• You and target opponent each create a Treasure token.
---
(Front): Adrift in the Aether</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/22_back.png" num="22b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Creature — Incarnation</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Adrift in the Aether</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Daiyu, of Three Houses</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance
When Daiyu, of Three Houses enters, if {B}{B} was spent to cast it, it enters with a Demon counter on it. (It is a Demon in addition to its other types.)
When Daiyu enters, if {R}{R} was spent to cast it, it enters with a Dragon counter on it. 
Demon creatures you control have lifelink.
Dragon creatures you control have haste.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/23.png" num="29">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Angel Noble</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4W</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WBR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shunpo Adept</name>
			<text>Flash
When this creature enters, tap up to one target creature.
{2}{W}, Discard a card: Return this creature to its owner&apos;s hand.
Warp {1}{W} (You may cast this card from your hand for its warp cost. Exile this creature at the beginning of the next end step, then you may cast it from exile on a later turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/24.png" num="58">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bewitching Serenade</name>
			<text>Enchant artifact or creature
When this Aura enters, tap enchanted permanent.
Enchanted permanent doesn&apos;t untap during its controller&apos;s untap step.
{5}{U}{U}: Untap enchanted permanent. Gain control of it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/25.png" num="69">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1UU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Box of Phanstasms</name>
			<text>Before you shuffle your deck to start the game, you may reveal this card from your deck and exile a creature card you drafted that isn&apos;t in your deck.
Exhaust — {U}, {T}: Copy a card you exiled with cards named Box of Phanstasms. You may cast the copy without paying its mana cost, except it&apos;s an Illusion in addition to its other types and has &quot;When this creature becomes the target of a spell, sacrifice it.&quot; (Activate each exhaust ability only once.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/26.png" num="70">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Shapeshifter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Decline // Prosecute</name>
			<text>Counter target spell unless its controller pays {3}. If they do, you investigate. (Create a Clue token. It&apos;s an artifact with &quot;{2}, Sacrifice this token: Draw a card.&quot;)

---

Aftermath (Cast this spell only from your graveyard. Then exile it.)
Return target creature to its owner&apos;s hand.
Addendum — If you cast this spell during your main phase, put that creature on top of its owner&apos;s library instead.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/27.png" num="77">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>aftermath</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant — Arcane</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1U // 2U</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shieldmage Field Officer</name>
			<text>Vigilance
When this creature enters, create a 1/1 blue Faerie creature token with flying. 
{U}, {T}, Tap another untapped creature you control: Put a shield counter on target creature. (If it would be dealt damage or destroyed, remove a shield counter from it instead.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/28.png" num="99">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dragon Soldier Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bitter Words</name>
			<text>Flash
Enchant creature
When this Aura enters, draw a card.
Enchanted creature gets +1/+1 and has afflict 1. (Whenever that creature becomes blocked, defending player loses 1 life.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/29.png" num="119">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>BB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dream Swindler</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, each opponent exiles the top card of their library or exiles a nonland card from their hand. You may play those cards for as long as they remain exiled, and mana of any type can be spent to cast them.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/30.png" num="132">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Nightmare Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4B</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rimepelt Packmate</name>
			<text>Offspring {1}{B} (You may pay an additional {1}{B} as you cast this spell. If you do, when this creature enters, create a 1/1 token copy of it.)
Menace</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/31.png" num="147">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Snow Creature — Wolf</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Soul Assimilator</name>
			<text>Mutate {1}{B} (If you cast this spell for its mutate cost, put it over or under target non-Human creature you own. They mutate into the creature on top plus all abilities from under it.)
Lifelink
When this creature enters and whenever it mutates, target player mills four cards. (They put the top four cards of their library into their graveyard.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/32.png" num="152">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>mutate</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dragon Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Trophy Kill</name>
			<text>Kicker {2} (You may pay an additional {2} as you cast this spell.)
Destroy target creature.
If this spell was kicked transfer the modifications from the destroyed creature onto a creature you control. You gain control of Auras and Equipments transferred to the creature you control this way. (Equipment, Auras, and counters are modifications.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/33.png" num="159">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Baptism of Draconic Ichor</name>
			<text>Kindred agenda (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose a creature type. You may turn this conspiracy face up any time and reveal the chosen type.)
Creatures you control of the chosen type have &quot;{R}, {T}: This creature deals 1 damage to any target&quot;.
Whenever you cast a Dragon spell, untap each creature you control of the chosen type.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/34.png" num="168">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Matchlight Spellweaver</name>
			<text>Prowess (Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, this creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
Firebending 2 (Whenever this creature attacks, add {R}{R}. This mana lasts until end of combat.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/35.png" num="189">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Squirrel Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Questing Zerdana</name>
			<text>First strike
When this creature leaves the battlefield, create a Fantasy token. (It&apos;s a red enchantment with &quot;{3}, Sacrifice this enchantment: Exile the top two cards of your library. Until the end of your next turn, you may play those cards. Activate only as a sorcery.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/36.png" num="196">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Fox Knight</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sage of Thermodynamics</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. After you draft this card, conjure three cards named Snow-Covered Mountain into your card pool.
Snowfall — Whenever you cast a snow spell or a snow land you control enters, put a +1/+1 counter on this creature.
{2}{S}{S}: This creature gets double strike until end of turn. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/37.png" num="198">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Call of the Verdant Hunt</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, Amass Wolves 1. (Put a +1/+1 counter on an Army you control. It&apos;s also a Wolf. If you don&apos;t control an Army, create a 0/0 black Wolf Army creature token first.)
Whenever one or more Wolf creatures you control deal combat damage to a player, draw a card.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, Amass Wolves 1.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/38.png" num="218">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Enchantment — Wolf</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Daydream Realized</name>
			<text>Target creature you control gets +2/+2 and gains trample until end of turn. Put a Dinosaur counter on it. (That creature is a Dinosaur in addition to its other types.)
Cycling {G} ({G}, Discard this card: Draw a card.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/39.png" num="225">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>GG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>The Spirit of Cartography</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. The player to your right chooses a basic land type other than Forest, then the player to your left chooses a third basic land type other than Forest.
When this enchantment enters, draw a card.
Forests you control are the chosen types in addition to their other types.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/40.png" num="252">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Anointed Tombship</name>
			<text>Flying
Crew 2 (Tap any number of creatures you control with total power 2 or more: This Vehicle becomes an artifact creature until end of turn.)
Morbid — At the beginning of your end step, if a creature died this turn, create a 2/2 black and red Knight creature token with &quot;This creature can&apos;t block.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/41.png" num="257">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Vehicle</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>2BR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BR</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Secret Alliance</name>
			<text>At the beginning of the first upkeep, create a player token immediately to your left with 1 life. For the rest of the game, you control that player. That player gets an emblem with &quot;If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, skip that draw instead.&quot;
At the beginning of each opponent&apos;s end step, each other player you control that didn&apos;t lose life this turn gains 1 life.
Whenever a player attacks you, that player loses X life, where X is the highest life total among other players you control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/42.png" num="16">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Oblivion Alliance</name>
			<text>Choose a creature. Create a player token immediately to your left with 1 life. For the rest of the game, you control that player. That player gets an emblem with &quot;If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, skip that draw instead.&quot; Exile the chosen creature until that player loses the game.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/43.png" num="49">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Senatorial Speaker</name>
			<text>Council&apos;s Dilemma — When this creature enters, starting with you, each player votes for aid or arms. For each aid vote, you and the voter each gain 2 life. For each arms vote. You and the voter each create a 1/1 white Soldier creature token.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/44.png" num="56">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WW</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Insightful Alliance</name>
			<text>Draw X cards. Create a player token immediately to your left with X life. For the rest of the game, you control that player. That player gets an emblem with &quot;If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, skip that draw instead.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/45.png" num="82">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>XUU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Masterminding</name>
			<text>You may cast spells from outside the game. As an additional cost to cast those spells, pay {U} and discard a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/46.png" num="88">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Political Riddler</name>
			<text>Undaunted (This spell costs {1} less to cast for each opponent.)
Flying; ward {3} (Whenever this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {3}.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/47.png" num="93">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Sphinx</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>8U</manacost>
				<cmc>9</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Walker of Time</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, each player creates a tapped blue artifact token named Fluxstone with &quot;{T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Target player takes an extra turn after this one. Activate only as a sorcery.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/48.png" num="109">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Wilted Intellectual</name>
			<text>When you cast this spell, if it wasn&apos;t cast from your hand, draw two cards.
Flashback {4}{U} (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it. It won&apos;t enter the battlefield when cast this way.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/49.png" num="112">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Horror</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3U</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bloodied Alliance</name>
			<text>Destroy target creature. Create a player token immediately to your left with X life, where X is that creature&apos;s mana value. For the rest of the game, you control that player. That player gets an emblem with &quot;If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, skip that draw instead.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/50.png" num="122">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Demon of Chronology</name>
			<text>Kicker—Skip your next turn. (You may skip your next turn in addition to any other costs as you cast this spell.)
Flying
When this creature enters, if it was kicked, put a finality counter on it and gain control of target player until the start of your next turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/51.png" num="129">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Demon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Demon of the Ringing Bell</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, each player conjures a card named Ghoulcaller&apos;s Bell onto the battlefield under their control. (A {1} artifact with &quot;{T}: Each player mills a card.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/52.png" num="130">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Demon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Feast of Rotting Brains</name>
			<text>Each opponent reveals their hand. Then, starting with you, each player votes for one of your opponents. For each time each player was voted for this way, you choose a card from that player&apos;s hand. They discard that card. Choose a card discarded this way. Conjure a copy of it into another player&apos;s hand, except its mana cost is {0}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/53.png" num="135">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Allied Pyromancy</name>
			<text>Kicker {1}{R} (You may pay an additional {1}{R} as you cast this spell.)
When you cast this spell, if it was kicked, copy it, then copy it an additional time for each other player you control. You may choose new targets for the copies.
This spell deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/54.png" num="164">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Inspirational Alliance</name>
			<text>You may reveal this card from your opening hand. If you do, Create a player token immediately to your left with 1 life. For the rest of the game, you control that player. That player gets an emblem with &quot;If you would draw a card while your library has no cards in it, skip that draw instead.&quot;
As an additional cost to cast this spell, discard a card, exile a conspiracy you control, or have a token player you control lose the game.
Draw two cards.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/55.png" num="187">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Spectral Searcher</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, each player conjures a card named Spectral Searchlight onto the battlefield under their control. (A {3} artifact with &quot;{T}: Choose a player. That player adds one mana of any color they choose.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/56.png" num="200">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Demon of Darkest Illusions</name>
			<text>Flying
As a player loses the game, choose a nonland permanent that player controls. Each other player creates a token that&apos;s a copy of it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/57.png" num="264">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Demon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Explosive Leylith</name>
			<text>If this card is in your opening hand, you may begin the game with it on the battlefield.
This artifact enters tapped.
{T}: Add {C}.
Channel — {7}, Discard this card: Destroy target nonland permanent.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/58.png" num="311">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cleaveland</name>
			<text>Cleave {2}{U}{R} (You may cast this spell for its cleave cost. If you do, remove the words in square brackets.)
{T}: Add {C}.
[{2}, ]{T}: Draw a card[, then discard a card].</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/59.png" num="330">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact [Land]</type>
				<maintype>[Land]</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Landscape Vault</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
As you draft a permanent card with mana value 3 or less, you may remove it from the draft, then turn this card face down.
This card has all abilities of cards you removed from the draft with cards named Landscape Vault.
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/60.png" num="332">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Blood</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {B} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/61.png" num="335">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Bone</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {W} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/62.png" num="336">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Darkness</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {U} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/63.png" num="337">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Death</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {B} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/64.png" num="338">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Fire</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {R} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/65.png" num="339">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Frost</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {W} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/66.png" num="340">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Life</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {G} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/67.png" num="341">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Light</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {R} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/68.png" num="342">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Thunder</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {U} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/69.png" num="343">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Metropolis of Water</name>
			<text>As this land enters, you may pay 2 life. If you don&apos;t, it enters tapped, and when it enters, surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
{T}: Add {G} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/70.png" num="344">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Janah, Her Own Worst Enemy</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
Before drawing your opening hand, each opponent may conjure a copy of this card into the command zone.
Whenever you attack, if one or more of those defending players own a vanguard named Janah, Her Own Worst Enemy, draw a card. Otherwise create a tapped treasure token and scry 1.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/71.png" num="10">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Vanguard</type>
				<maintype>Vanguard</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<pt>-1/-3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tyrannical Ruler</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, you become the monarch.
As long as you&apos;re the monarch, noncreature spells your opponents cast cost {1} more to cast.
Disturb {1}{W} (You may cast this card from your graveyard transformed for its disturb cost.)
---
(Back): Heavy Is The Crown</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/72_front.png" num="65a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Noble</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Heavy Is The Crown</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Heavy Is The Crown</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, target player becomes the monarch.
Noncreature spells the monarch casts cost {1} more to cast.
If this enchantment would be put into a graveyard from anywhere, exile it instead.
---
(Front): Tyrannical Ruler</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/72_back.png" num="65b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Tyrannical Ruler</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Grizwold, Phantasmal Druid</name>
			<text>[+1]: Until your next turn, up to one target creature gets -1/-0.
[-2]: Create a Phantasmal Bear token. (It&apos;s a {U} 2/2 Bear Illusion creature with &quot;When this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability, sacrifice it.&quot;)
[-6]: You get an emblem with &quot;Each creature you don&apos;t control is an Illusion in addition to its other types and has ‘When this creature becomes the target of a spell or ability, sacrifice it.&apos;&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/73.png" num="81">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Grizwold</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>3</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Corruption Killer</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, that player loses life equal to the number of conspiracies they own in the command zone.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/74.png" num="126">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Zombie Assassin</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Don&apos;t Mine At Night</name>
			<text>Target creature gets -2/-2 until end of turn. If it&apos;s night, destroy that creature instead.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/75.png" num="131">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>B</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gift of Decay</name>
			<text>Gift a Rotting Regisaur (You may promise an opponent a gift as you cast this spell. If you do, they create a Rotting Regisaur before its other effects. It&apos;s a {2}{B} 7/6 Zombie Dinosaur creature with &quot;At the beginning of your upkeep, discard a card.&quot;)
When this enchantment enters, if the gift was promised, create a Rotting Regisaur token.
Whenever an opponent discards one or more cards, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/76.png" num="137">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2B</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Soul-Infused Butcher</name>
			<text>As an additional cost to cast this spell, you may sacrifice a creature with power 5 or greater. If you do, this spell costs {5} less to cast.
Flying
When this creature enters, target player draws two cards and loses 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/77.png" num="153">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Demon Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5BB</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Super Booster Tutor</name>
			<text>Draft Super Booster Tutor face up.
After you draft a card from a pack, you may turn Super Booster Tutor face down. When you do, note the name of each other card in the pack. Add those cards to the spellbook of cards you drafted named Super Booster Tutor. (You can do this with the pack you drafted this from.)
You may conjure a card of your choice from Super Booster Tutor&apos;s spellbook into your hand. If you don&apos;t, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/78.png" num="156">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Viral Replication</name>
			<text>Create a 1/1 black Virus creature token with menace. Conjure a copy of Viral Replication into exile and encode it onto that token.
Cipher (Then you may exile this spell card encoded on a creature you control. Whenever that creature deals combat damage to a player, its controller may cast a copy of the encoded card without paying its mana cost.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/79.png" num="161">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Consuming Wildfire</name>
			<text>Haste
{T}: Target creature gets +1/+0 until end of turn. Activate only as a sorcery.
Forecast — {2}{R}, Reveal Consuming Wildfire from your hand: Conjure a copy of Consuming Inferno into your hand. (Activate only during your upkeep and only once each turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/80.png" num="171">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Crackling Titan</name>
			<text>Slumber 2 — 1R
Menace
Whenever one or more stun counters are removed from this creature, conjure a card named Shock into your hand. (Shock is a {R} instant with &quot;Shock deals 2 damage to any target.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/81.png" num="172">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Giant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Diabolic Instigator</name>
			<text>(As this enters and as you untap, this isn&apos;t a battle until end of turn. As each opponent untaps, this isn&apos;t a creature until end of turn. As long as this is a battle, you protect it.)
Flying, haste
Whenever this creature enters or attacks, goad target creature. (Until your next turn, that creature attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.) [4/3]</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/82.png" num="173">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Battle Creature — Boss Demon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>6</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gangnam Style</name>
			<text>Tempting Offer — When you cast this spell, each opponent may copy it. For each opponent who does, copy this spell. Players may choose new targets for the copies.
Target creature gets +3/+1 and gains horsemanship until end of turn. (That creature can&apos;t be blocked except by creatures with horsemanship.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/83.png" num="178">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Overthrowing Riot</name>
			<text>The first creature spell you cast each turn has riot. (That creature enters with your choice of a +1/+1 counter or haste.)
Creatures you control have dethrone. (Whenever that creature attacks the player with the most life or tied for most life, put a +1/+1 counter on it.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/84.png" num="193">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Super Chaos Warp</name>
			<text>Draft Super Chaos Warp face up.
As you draft a card, you may remove that card from the draft. If you do, turn Super Chaos Warp face down, and add a random card from another Strata Games BOO cube to your card pool.
The owner of target nonenchantment permanent shuffles it into their library, then conjures a random card from another Strata Games BOO cube into the command zone. If it&apos;s a land card, they put it onto the battlefield. Otherwise, they may cast it without paying its mana cost.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/85.png" num="201">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Plump Kingslayer</name>
			<text>Trample
Dethrone (Whenever this creature attacks the player with the most life or tied for most life, put a +1/+1 counter on it.)
When this creature enters, you become the monarch.
Whenever a player becomes the monarch, they gain 3 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/86.png" num="243">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Boar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Greedy Dungeon-Delver</name>
			<text>When this creature enters or attacks, conjure a random card from its spellbook onto the battlefield tapped.
Whenever a player conjures one or more cards, each opponent loses 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/87.png" num="268">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Kobold Pirate</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BR</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Methri, Cruel Usurper</name>
			<text>When Methri, Cruel Usurper enters, you become the monarch.
Whenever you become the monarch, you get an emblem with &quot;At the beginning of the monarch&apos;s end step, each of the monarch&apos;s opponents lose 1 life and the monarch gains 1 life.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/88.png" num="277">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Noble</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UBR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UBR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UBR</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Random Loot Drop</name>
			<text>Conjure two random cards from among Strata Games BOO cubes into the command zone. You may play them until the end of your next turn and may spend mana as though it were mana of any type to cast spells this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/89.png" num="287">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>BR</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>BR</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Abandoned Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {R} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/90.png" num="326">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Airborn Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {W} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/91.png" num="327">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Arid Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {R} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/92.png" num="329">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lush Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {G} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/93.png" num="333">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mechanical Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {U} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/94.png" num="334">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Molten Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {B} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/95.png" num="345">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nefarious Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {B} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/96.png" num="346">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rotten Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {U} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/97.png" num="357">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ruinous Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {W} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/98.png" num="358">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Venerable Stronghold</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped unless an opponent is the monarch or has the initiative.
{T}: Add {G} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/99.png" num="360">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land — Lair</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dungeon Delve</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. 
You may remove another common or uncommon instant or sorcery card from the draft face up as you draft it and turn this card face down. If you do, the instant or sorcery card becomes a dungeon, and its only room is its rules text. (It loses all other card types. Only you may enter it. After entering, leave it.)
Target player may venture into the dungeon, then they may take the initiative. (They may enter the first room or advance to the next room.)
(Then shuffle card this into its owner&apos;s library.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/100.png" num="33">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery — Omen</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Self Defense Training</name>
			<text>(Nonexistent mana costs can&apos;t be paid.)
Aid (Other players may pay for the generic mana costs of this spell.)
Destroy target creature if it attacked this turn. When that creature attacks this turn, destroy it.
Splice onto a non-permanent spell you paid for {W} (After a player floats their mana to cast an instant or sorcery spell, you may reveal this card, pay {W} and any amount of that spells generic mana cost. If you pay at least two mana this way, that spell&apos;s controller adds this card&apos;s text to the end of their spell, meaning other players may pay for the remaining generic mana costs of that spell. After that spell&apos;s caster pays for the remaining costs, they may undo any number of mana abilities that can be undone. You chose the target for this card&apos;s ability on that spell.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/101.png" num="54">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant — Lesson</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Naritive Fracture // </name>
			<text>Undaunted (This spell costs {1} less to cast for each opponent.)
Counter target spell from a Universe Beyond. (A card is from a Universe Beyond if it&apos;s first printing depicts a property copyrighted by a company other than Wizards of the Coast.)

---

Draft this card face up.
You may remove a sorcery card from the draft face up as you draft it. If you do, turn this card face down, and that sorcery card becomes this card&apos;s omen, except it costs {U} more to cast.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/102.png" num="90">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant — Lesson // Sorcery — Omen</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3U/P // </manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Spellshaper&apos;s Reversal</name>
			<text>Discard a card with mana value X: Counter target spell with mana value X. Activate only once and only if Spellshaper&apos;s Reversal is on the stack
Discard a card with power X: Return target creature with toughness X to its owners hand. Activate only once and only if Spellshaper&apos;s Reversal is on the stuck.
Draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/103.png" num="101">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Instant — Spellshaper</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Stolen Seconds</name>
			<text>You may pay {1}{U} as your turn ends. If you do, swap positions in turn order with the player before you. (This doesn&apos;t change who takes the next turn. Spend mana only from mana abilities that were activated or triggered as your turn ends. Any non-mana triggered abilities that trigger are put onto the stack during the next turn&apos;s upkeep.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/104.png" num="102">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Vrnkjkt, Potential Mage</name>
			<text>{X}{U}, {T}, Discard a card: One or two target nonland permanents you don&apos;t control each with mana value X or less becomes nonpermanent. (They can&apos;t be tapped, transformed, flipped, phased out, face down, attacked, destroyed, or sacrificed. They can&apos;t attack, block, conspire, or explore. They&apos;re not affected by effects that refer to them by type, including targeting, state based actions, etc. They still have their abilities.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/105.png" num="108">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Homunculus Spellshaper</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Guild Master Facade</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. After you draft this card, you may draft another creature card that isn&apos;t rare or mythic and note its name.
You may have a creature card with a name you noted for cards named Guild Master Facade as your commander. That card and cards you own that aren&apos;t included in that card&apos;s color identity cost {B} and 2 life more to cast.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/106.png" num="140">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shambling Corpse</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. 
You may remove another card from the draft face up as you draft it and turn this card face down. If you do, conjure a card named Murder into your card pool. (It&apos;s a {1}{B}{B} instant with &quot;Destroy target creature.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/107.png" num="149">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Zombie</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Chaotic Wrapper</name>
			<text>This card can&apos;t be your first, second, or third pick of the first draft round. (It can be the first, second, or third pick of any further draft rounds.)
Reveal this card as you draft it. After you draft this card, each player puts a face down card from their card pool into a single pile. Add that pile to the draft as a pack. (Your next pick is from that pack. It&apos;s drafted this round.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/108.png" num="170">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Beast Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Illicit Markets</name>
			<text>Once each pick, you may reveal this card from a pack you are looking at. If you do, you can&apos;t draft this card this pick, and you may draft an additional card from this booster pack by revealing two cards from your card pool, putting them into this booster pack, and increasing the noted number of this card by one. (It starts at 0.)
{1}{R}: Up to X target creatures get +1/+0 for each {R} spent on this, where X is the noted number.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/109.png" num="186">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Service Dog</name>
			<text>Visit — Put a level counter on this creature. [1/2]
[level 1-2] Visit — Creatures you control gain trample and haste until end of turn. [3/2]
[level 3+] Visit — Creatures you control get +X/+X and gain trample and haste until end of turn, where X is this creatures level. The same is true of creatures that enter under your control this turn. [4/2]</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/110.png" num="199">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Attraction Dog Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Centaur Skirmisher</name>
			<text>Banding, banding, banding, provoke, provoke, flanking, flanking (This can attack in a band with any number of creatures equal to or less than one plus the total number of instances of banding between all of them. If any creatures with banding you control are blocking or being blocked by a creature, you divide that creature&apos;s combat damage, not its controller, among any of the creatures it&apos;s being blocked by or is blocking. When this creature attacks, you may have up to two target creatures defending player controls block this creature if able. Whenever a creature without flanking blocks this creature, that creature gets -2/-2 until end of turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/111.png" num="219">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Centaur Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Denaturalize</name>
			<text>Choose the name of target creature. Named creatures get +2/+2 until end of turn. (A creature is named if its name has been chosen this game.)
Until end of turn, damage dealt to you, an object you control, or an object you protect goes on the stack. (It&apos;s put on the stack when it would have been dealt. It&apos;s not a spell or ability. When it resolves, the damage is dealt.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/112.png" num="227">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Destined Champion</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up. 
As you draft a single-faced green creature card, you may remove it from the draft face up and turn this card face down. If you do, that card becomes this card&apos;s front face, except it has &quot;When this creature dies, you may exile it. If you do, you may cast it transformed for as long as it remains exiled.&quot;
---
(Back): Colossal Dreadmount</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/113_front.png" num="228a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Colossal Dreadmount</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Colossal Dreadmount</name>
			<text>Whenever this creature becomes saddled for the first time each turn, it gains trample and absorb 1 until end of turn. (If a source would deal damage to this creature, prevent 1 of that damage.)
Saddle 3 (Tap any number of other creatures you control with total power 3 or more: This Mount becomes saddled until end of turn. Saddle only as a sorcery.)
---
(Front): Destined Champion</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/113_back.png" num="228b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur Mount</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Destined Champion</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pheldagrif, Returned Quester</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, you may search your library for a named creature card, put it into your hand, then shuffle. (A card is named if it&apos;s name has been chosen this game.)
This creature has your choice of lifelink or trample. If you control a named creature, you may choose for it may have both. (You may change your choice at any time, even if you don&apos;t have priority.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/114.png" num="281">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Phelddagrif</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Phelddagrif&apos;s Assistance</name>
			<text>(Kindred spells can&apos;t be played. They remain on the stack to resolve again as they resolve.)
Whenever you reveal this card, draw a card. (If you reveal this card while drafting, draw a card during the draft by adding a random card not in a booster pack to your card pool.)
Forecast — {W}{B}{G}, Reveal this card from your hand, Pay 1 life: Support 1. (Activate only during your upkeep and only once each turn. To support 1, put a +1/+1 counter on up to one target creature.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/115.png" num="282">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred — Phelddagrif</type>
				<maintype>Kindred</maintype>
				<manacost>WBG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>WBG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WBG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Radiance Rekindled</name>
			<text>Choose two —
• Change this card&apos;s text by replacing each instance of &quot;target creature&quot; with &quot;target creature and any number of other creatures of your choice that share a color with it.&quot; (They aren&apos;t targets.)
• Radiance Rekindled deals 2 damage to target creature.
• Target creature get +1/+1 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/116.png" num="285">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>UR</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sphinx Delegate</name>
			<text>Gift control of this spell. (You may promise an opponent a gift as you cast this spell. If you do, that opponent gains control of this spell as it resolves. It enters under their control.)
Flying
Adamant — When this creature enters, if three of the same mana pip type was spent to cast it, your life total becomes 10. (Three mana of the same color, colorless mana, or snow mana.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/117.png" num="322">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Sphinx Child</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ilythræ, City of Peace</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
Immediately after the draft, each other player chooses a card name. Note those names.
Partner with a card you noted for cards named Ilythræ, City of Peace. (When this enters, choose a noted card name. Target player may put a card with that name into their hand from their library, then shuffle. If a noted card is your commander, this can be your second commander.)
{T}: Add {C}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/118.png" num="331">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Grasping Ephemeration</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. Each player reveals the next card they draft. When each player has revealed a card this way, you may exchange this card with a card revealed this way.
This card must be in your deck if it&apos;s in your card pool.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/119.png" num="8">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Illusion</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<pt>0/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hushed Whispers</name>
			<text>Special agenda (After drafting this card, as another player reveals a card while drafting, secretly note the revealed card&apos;s name. Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. You may turn this face up any time and reveal each of the noted names.)
Whenever a player casts a spell with a named noted while drafting cards named Hushed Whispers, you may pay {2}. When you do, counter that spell.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/120.png" num="9">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shocking Reanimation</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
The first time you would lose the game, you may instead have your life total become 1 and exile each permanent you control and each card in your hand. Until the beginning of your next main phase, your life total can&apos;t change. At the beginning of your next main phase, draw cards equal to the number of cards in your library.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/121.png" num="17">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Silent Poltergeist</name>
			<text>When this creature dies, return it to the battlefield with a finality counter on it. (If a creature with a finality counter on it would die, exile it instead.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/122.png" num="18">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Divine Interventionist</name>
			<text>Exhaust — {W}: Untap this creature. It gets +3/+0 and gains flying and lifelink until end of turn. Activate only during your turn. (Activate each exhaust ability only once.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/123.png" num="31">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Angel Cleric</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Systematic Incubation</name>
			<text>Enchant creature
If enchanted creature would attack, you may instead create a token that&apos;s a copy of it tapped and attacking. At the beginning of your next end step, the token loses all types and abilities and becomes an artifact named Scrap.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/124.png" num="62">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mama Bird</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance
When this creature dies, you may put a flying counter and a vigilance counter on target creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/125.png" num="87">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Reach Deep</name>
			<text>Scry 2.
Manifest the top card of your library, then draw a card. (To manifest a card, put it onto the battlefield face down as a 2/2 creature. Turn it face up any time for its mana cost if it&apos;s a creature card.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/126.png" num="96">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Afterlife Punisher</name>
			<text>Lifelink and deathtouch to creatures cast from exile. (If this is in your deck, it&apos;s your obligation to keep track of what creatures were cast from exile. This means you, Mark.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/127.png" num="114">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Skeleton Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cut Up</name>
			<text>Destroy target creature with total power and toughness 5 or greater.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/128.png" num="128">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Archer Comrade</name>
			<text>This creature enters with a ranged counter on it. (Prevent all combat damage dealt to a creature with ranged if its attacking with at least one other creature without ranged.)
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player while attacking with another creature, you may move a ranged counter from it onto another target attacking creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/129.png" num="167">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elf Archer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Harmonize Crystallize</name>
			<text>Gain control of target creature until end of turn. Untap that creature. It gains haste until end of turn. When it dies this turn, create two tapped Powerstone tokens. (They&apos;re artifacts with &quot;{T}: Add {C}. This mana can&apos;t be spent to cast a nonartifact spell.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/130.png" num="182">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Choice of the Woods</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, draw a card and reveal it. If the revealed card isn&apos;t a creature card, discard it.
Whenever you draw a creature card, you may reveal it and pay {3}. When you do, discard it, then search your library for a card with the same mana value as that card, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/131.png" num="220">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Off-Duty Janitor</name>
			<text>Trample
When this creatures enters, you may move all +1/+1 counters from creatures you don&apos;t control onto this creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/132.png" num="239">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Citizen Knight</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bloodied Dagger</name>
			<text>Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage to a player, you may distribute that many -1/-1 counters among creatures that player controls.
Equip {1} ({1}: Attach to target creature you control. Equip only as a sorcery.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/133.png" num="308">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Equipment</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Collapse Traveler</name>
			<text>Vanishing 8 (This creature enters with eight time counters on it. At the beginning of your upkeep, remove a time counter from it. When the last is removed, sacrifice it.)
Whenever a time counter is removed from this creature, add {C}. Until this creature leaves the battlefield, you don&apos;t lose this mana as steps and phases end.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/134.png" num="309">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Nomad Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<pt>3/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Extraction Cage</name>
			<text>When this artifact enters, exile target creature.
Exhaust — {3}: Target creature you control loses all abilities and gains the abilities of all creatures cards exiled with this artifact. (Activate each exhaust ability only once. This effect lasts indefinitely.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/135.png" num="312">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>6</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Makeshift Configuration</name>
			<text>Reveal this card and the next three cards as you draft them. Note the first&apos;s mana value, the second&apos;s power, and the third&apos;s toughness. (Picking a card with no mana cost or no stats leads to a value of 0.)
X is equal to the highest mana value noted as you drafted cards named Makeshift Configuration. The same is true for Y and highest power noted, and Z and highest toughness noted.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/136.png" num="316">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>X</manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<pt>Y/Z</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Scrapyard Bartender</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. Choose a mana value, then each player starts a tab. As a player drafts a card of that mana value, they may reveal that card and add 1 to their tab.
When this creature enters, each player creates X Food tokens, where X is their tab.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/137.png" num="319">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Shapeshifter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Scuttler Drone</name>
			<text>Modular 2 (This creature enters with two +1/+1 counters on it. When it dies, you may put its +1/+1 counters on target artifact creature.)
Equipped creature gets +1/+1 for each +1/+1 counter on this creature.
Reconfigure—{1}, Pay 1 life for each +1/+1 counter on this creature ({1}, Pay 1 life for each +1/+1 counter on this creature: Attach to target creature you control; or unattach from a creature. Reconfigure only as a sorcery. While attached, this isn&apos;t a creature.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/138.png" num="320">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct Insect</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<pt>0/0</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Seer of Fates</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. Reveal the next card you draft and note its name.
When this creature enters, you may put a card with the noted name that you drafted and isn&apos;t in your library on top of your library. (From anywhere that isn&apos;t your library, including outside the game.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/139.png" num="321">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Origin of the Spark</name>
			<text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter.)
Create a 2/2 Human creature token that&apos;s all colors.
Put three loyalty counters on up to one target creature or planeswalker you control. It gains &quot;l[-1]: Planeswalk&quot; and &quot;l[-3]: Chaos Ensues.&quot;
III — Put Origin of the Spark into the command zone perpetually transformed.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/140.png" num="13">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>saga</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Enchantment — Saga</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Traiterous Hobbyism</name>
			<text>If you would draw a card during your turn, you may instead draft a card from the Hobby Traitor&apos;s Spellbook.
{2}: Add one mana of any color. Spend this mana only to cast spells from a non-Magic the Gathering™ property. (Hobby Traitor&apos;s Spellbook spells, Universe Beyond spells, etc.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/141.png" num="20">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Electoral Officer</name>
			<text>{2}: Electoral Officer&apos;s controller ventures into The Forum. Any player may activate this ability, but only once each turn and only as a sorcery.
Whenever players finish voting, you and each other player that voted for a choice you voted for create a 1/1 green and white Citizen creature token. If you have the city&apos;s blessing, you may create a 1/1 white Soldier creature token with lifelink instead.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/142.png" num="34">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Inspiring Virtuoso</name>
			<text>Vigilance, banding (You&apos;ll figure it out.)
Immortal Symphony — Whenever another creature you control attacks or blocks in a band with Inspiring Virtuoso, it perpetually gains banding and encore. It&apos;s encore cost is equal to its mana cost plus {2}.
Encore {3}{W} ({3}{W}, Exile this card from your graveyard: For each opponent, create a token copy that attacks that opponent this turn if able. They gain haste. Sacrifice them at the beginning of the next end step. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/143.png" num="42">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Bard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mystical Menagerie</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
As you draft a creature card that doesn&apos;t share a subtype with a card in your card pool, it perpetually gains &quot;This spell costs {1} less to cast.&quot;
Non-Human creatures you control get +1/+1 and have ward {X}, where X is the number of subtypes it has. (Whenever this permanent becomes the target of a spell or ability an opponent controls, counter it unless that player pays {X}.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/144.png" num="45">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Necrotheistic Catechism</name>
			<text>Yield {WB}{WB}{WB} (You may cast this spell for its yield cost. If you do, an opponent chooses the modes. You still choose the targets.)
Choose one or both —
• Destroy target creature if its attacking or blocking.
• Choose a creature card in a graveyard that was put there from the battlefield this turn. Put it onto the battlefield under your control.
You may cast Necrotheistic Catechism from your graveyard for it&apos;s yield cost. If you do, exile it as it resolves.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/145.png" num="47">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant — Lesson</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tyrant of the Broken Seals</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance
When Tyrant of the Broken Seals dies, create a Seal of Cleansing token, a Seal of Removal token, a Seal of Doom token, a Seal of Fire token, and a Seal of Strength token. (They&apos;re officially printed cards you can find by searching.)
Evoke {W}{U}{B}{R}{G} (You may cast this spell for its evoke cost. If you do, it&apos;s sacrificed when it enters.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/146.png" num="66">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dragon Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Essence of Nothing</name>
			<text>Bestow {4}{U} (If you cast this card for its bestow cost, it&apos;s an Aura spell with enchant creature. It becomes a creature again if it&apos;s not attached.)
Myriad (Whenever this creature attacks, for each opponent other than defending player, you may create a token that&apos;s a copy of this creature that&apos;s tapped and attacking that player or a planeswalker they control. Exile the tokens at end of combat.)
This creature can&apos;t be blocked.
Enchanted creature gets +1/+1, has myriad and &quot;This creature and each other creature with the same name as it can&apos;t be blocked.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/147.png" num="78">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment Creature — Illusion</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ogmog the Space Frog</name>
			<text>Ogmog the Space Frog enters tapped with an infinite number of stun counters on it. (You technically need to pick a number. One million or so will probably be enough.)
Whenever you remove one or more counters from Ogmog, create a 1/1 colorless Robot artifact creature token.
Whenever one or more artifact creatures you control deal combat damage to an opponent, Ogmog becomes attacking.
Last strike (This creature deals combat damage after creatures without last strike.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/148.png" num="92">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Alien Frog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bessyl, Vaul&apos;s Protige</name>
			<text>Draft Bessyl, Vaul&apos;s Protige face up.
As you draft a card, you may remove it from the draft face up. Bessyl gains all loyalty abilities of that card. (Those cards aren&apos;t in your card pool.)
Spark X, where X one plus the number of cards removed from the draft with cards named Bessyl, Vaul&apos;s Protige.
[level -1] You draw a card and you lose 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/149.png" num="118">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Troll Berserker</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Black Masquerade</name>
			<text>Creatures you control have mimic. (As a creature enters under your control, choose a creature type. It becomes that creature type in addition to its other types.)
Whenever a creature you control dies, you may pay {B}. If you do, put a -1/-1 counter on target creature that shares a creature type with it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/150.png" num="120">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Junkyard Enthusiast // Scraps for Swarm</name>
			<text>When Junkyard Enthusiast enters, create a Food token.
Miracle {0} (You may cast this card for its miracle cost when you draw it if it&apos;s the first card you drew this turn.)
Conjure a duplicate of Junkyard Enthusiast into your hand.
(Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, you may cast a copy of its Malware by paying the Malware&apos;s costs. Malware can only be cast this way.)

---

Choose one —
• Create a Food token.
• Create a Junk token.
• Create a Clue token.
• Create a Powerstone token.
Conjure a duplicate of Junkyard Enthusiast into your hand.
(Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, you may cast a copy of its Malware by paying the Malware&apos;s costs. Malware can only be cast this way.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/151.png" num="141">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Rat // Instant — Adventure</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>B // B</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Murder Trial</name>
			<text>Put target creature into a graveyard. It died last turn (it doesn&apos;t trigger abilities from dying.) That creature&apos;s controller may collect evidence 7. If they do, each player creates a Clue token and votes for which creature they think is guilty of the crime. Then, the destroyed creatures controller chooses a creature with the most votes or tied for the most votes and detains it for 25 turns. (For 25 turns, that creature can&apos;t attack or block and its abilities can&apos;t be activated.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/152.png" num="146">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Sorcery — Assassin or Detective</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>BB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Taj, Living Malignancy</name>
			<text>When Taj, Living Malignancy enters or attacks, each player mills a card. Then you may have up to three cards from among graveyards perpetually become a copy of Taj. If you do, those cards are shuffled into their owners library.
Grandeur — Pay {1} or 2 life, Discard another card named Taj, Living Malignancy: Create a 1/1 black Thrull creature token.
Cycling—Pay {1} or 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/153.png" num="157">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Thrull</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Magic Incarnate</name>
			<text>Choose four —
• This spell and target permanent gain haste.
• This spell and target permanent gain melee.
• This spell and target permanent gain menace.
• This spell and target permanent gain first strike.
• This spell and target permanent get +2/+2.
• This spell and target permanent you control become creatures. (They lose all other card types.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/154.png" num="188">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery — Arcane</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ake &amp; Ke&apos;an, Colossal Duo</name>
			<text>Trample
Dreadmaw creatures you control have ward {2}.
At the beginning of your upkeep, choose the name of a Dreadmaw creature card and conjure a card of that name into exile. You may cast that card until end of turn, and you may cast it without paying its mana cost if Ake &amp; Ke&apos;an dealt 3 or more combat damage to an opponent this turn. (A Dreadmaw is a creature with base power and toughness 6/6 and trample.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/155.png" num="212">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4GG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Banana Vendor</name>
			<text>Reach (He&apos;s got them Tree Climbing Grippers™.)
When this creature enters, roll to visit your attractions. 
(Also do this every turn as your main phase begins. Visit all of your attractions with the result lit up. The lights are over there —&gt;)
Visit — Each player creates two colorless artifact tokens named Banana with &quot;{T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Add {R} or {G}. You gain 2 life.&quot; Then if you control the most artifacts, claim the prize!
Prize — You may sacrifice this artifact and any number of other artifacts. If you do, create a 2/2 green Monkey creature token for each artifact sacrificed this way. (Monke. heh.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/156.png" num="216">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Monkey Attraction</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kid, Quickshot Captain</name>
			<text>Whenever a creature you control with haste deals combat damage to a player, create a Treasure token.
[+1]: Conjure a random card with blitz into your hand. It perpetually gains &quot;You may spend mana as though it were any type to pay blitz costs of this spell.&quot;
[-2]: Target creature you control gains myriad until end of turn. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.
[-6]: You get an emblem with &quot;Creatures you control with haste can&apos;t be blocked&quot; and &quot;Creatures you control can&apos;t be sacrificed.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/157.png" num="273">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Kid</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>1RWB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WBR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WBR</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Strixhaven Socialite</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
Whenever Strixhaven Socialite enters or attacks, create a Scroll token. (It&apos;s an artifact with &quot;{2}, {T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Cast a copy of a card inscribed on this artifact without paying its mana cost.)
Whenever a creature an opponent controls dies, you may exile up to one target instant or sorcery card from that creatures controllers graveyard inscribed on a Scroll you control. Do this only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/158.png" num="295">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Vampire Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Garden of Life // Arbor of Death</name>
			<text>When you unlock this door, put a lifelink counter on up to one target creature.
Whenever you gain life, you may exile the top card of your library with a Rebirth counter on it.
At the beginning of your upkeep, if both doors of this permanent are unlocked, you may pay {WB}{WB}. If you do, transform it.

---

When you unlock this door, put a deathtouch counter on up to one target creature.
Whenever an opponent loses life, you may exile the top card of that players library with a Rebirth counter on it.
At the beginning of your upkeep, if both doors of this permanent are unlocked, you may pay {WB}{WB}. If you do, transform it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/159.png" num="305">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>split</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Room</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1W // 1B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Exploration Installation</name>
			<text>Scouting Mission — When this Fortification becomes attached to a land and at the beginning of your upkeep, untap fortified land. You gain control of that land until end of turn.
Whenever fortified land is tapped for mana, its controller adds an additional one mana of any type it could produce.
{3}, {T}: Attach Exploration Installation to target land. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/160.png" num="310">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Lander Fortification</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>1</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Chronomatic Skyscape</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
On each player&apos;s first turn, that player draws an additional card during their draw step and they may play an additional land that turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/161.png" num="2">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Riddlestrix</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it and note how many cards remain in this booster pack.
[Noted 0-3] Flying, vigilance [4/4]
[Noted 4+] Flying [3/3]</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/162.png" num="14">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Aberetta Shield</name>
			<text>Defender
Exalted (Whenever a creature you control attacks alone, that creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
When this creature enters, create a 1/1 white Human Soldier creature token with first strike.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/163.png" num="21">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Call for a Hero</name>
			<text>Choose one —
• Destroy target creature with power 4 or greater.
• Put a +1/+1 counter on target creature you control. It fights target creature you don&apos;t control with power 4 or greater.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/164.png" num="26">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gubbug, Paladindrome</name>
			<text>Gubbug has first strike and lifelink as long as an opponent has one or more cards in their hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/165.png" num="39">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Knight</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nestlings</name>
			<text>Flying
When Nestlings comes into play, you gain 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/166.png" num="48">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Abyssal Wobli</name>
			<text>Whenever this creature deals combat damage to player, that player gets an emblem with &quot;Your maximum hand size is reduced by one.&quot;
{3}: Put a +1/+1 counter on this creature. Activate only as a sorcery.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/167.png" num="67">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Jellyfish Demon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Storm Drake</name>
			<text>Flying
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, draw a card then discard a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/168.png" num="103">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental Drake</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Think Again</name>
			<text>Tiered (Choose one additional cost.)
Choose target spell or ability with a single target. Then, choose one—
• Revision — {0} — Its controller changes the target.
• Misdirection — {3} — Change the target.
• Amplification — {6} — For each other target that it could target, copy it. Each copy targets a different one of those targets.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/169.png" num="105">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Blackleaf Cultist</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, put a decayed counter on target creature. (It can&apos;t block. When it attacks, sacrifice it at end of combat.)
Whenever a player sacrifices a permanent, they lose 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/170.png" num="121">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elf Shaman</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Surprise Jackal!</name>
			<text>Sneak {2}{R}{R} (You may cast this spell for {2}{R}{R} if you also return an unblocked attacker you control to hand during the declare blockers step. It enters tapped and attacking.)
When this creature enters, for each player, exile target instant or sorcery card from that player&apos;s graveyard.
Once during each of your turns, you may cast a card exiled with this creature without paying its mana cost.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/171.png" num="202">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Jackal Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4R</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Angle of Attack</name>
			<text>Angle of Attack deals 90 damage to target creature or planeswalker. If that creature or planeswalker would die this turn, exile it instead.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/172.png" num="165">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>4R</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Overexert</name>
			<text>Target creature gets +5/+1 and gains trample until end of turn. Put a -1/-1 counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/173.png" num="192">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Terra Elemental</name>
			<text>Exhaust — {3}{R}, Sacrifice a Mountain: Terra Elemental deals 4 damage to any target. (Activate each exhaust ability only once.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/174.png" num="205">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Baloth Matriarch</name>
			<text>Offspring {2} (You may pay an additional {2} as you cast this spell. If you do, when this creature enters, create a 1/1 token copy of it.)
Trample
Whenever this creature attacks, put a +1/+1 on target Beast you control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/175.png" num="215">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Beast</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2GG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Heinous Flytrap</name>
			<text>Reach, deathtouch
Whenever a creature dealt damage by this creature this turn dies, create a Blood token. (It&apos;s an artifact with &quot;{1}, {T}, Discard a card, Sacrifice this token: Draw a card.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/176.png" num="234">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spider Mutant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Savannah Ram</name>
			<text>Trample, haste
Whenever this creature attacks, it gets +1/+1 until end of turn for each player who controls a nonbasic land.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/177.png" num="246">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Sheep</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sonomance Expon</name>
			<text>Create an Equipment artifact token named Scale. It has &quot;Equipped creature gets +1/+1 for each Equipment named Scale equipped to it,&quot; and &quot;Equip {1}.&quot;
Flashback {1}{G} (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/178.png" num="251">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Chiss, Tangle Transmuter</name>
			<text>At the beginning of your end step, create a Potion token. (An artifact with &quot;{1}, {T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Target creature.&quot;)
Whenever a Potion you control targets a creature, you may have that creature get +1/+1 and gain flying and haste until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/179.png" num="261">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>GUR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>URG</colors>
				<coloridentity>URG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rebellious Outcrier</name>
			<text>Flying
When this creature enters, draw a card. Target opponent discards a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/180.png" num="288">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Faerie Rebel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rockjaw Rising</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, and at the beginning of your upkeep, create a 2/2 green Crocodile creature token.
As long as you control four or more Islands, Crocodiles you control get +1/+1 and have menace.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/181.png" num="290">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>GGUU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Null Pointer</name>
			<text>As this spell resolves, put this card into your mana pool. (Put it into your graveyard only once its mana is spent.)
This card is mana of the amounts and types of the most recent mana you&apos;ve lost. (For example, if you lose {R}{R}, then lose {C}{B}{B}, this is {C}{B}{B}. Spending mana isn&apos;t losing it. )
You must spend this card&apos;s mana all at once. (For example, if this is {W}{U}{R}, you can&apos;t use it to pay for {2}.)
You don&apos;t lose this card&apos;s mana as steps and phases end.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/182.png" num="12">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Mana Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Coilmaster Ringmaster</name>
			<text>Assist (Another player can pay up to {4} of this spell&apos;s cost.)
If another player spent 4 or more mana while assisting this creature, it enters under their control.
At the beginning of your upkeep, if you have fewer than three cards in hand, draw equal to the difference, then Coilmaster Ringmaster&apos;s owner gains control of it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/183.png" num="27">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Snake Performer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4W</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Courting Courchevelia</name>
			<text>Players play with the top cards of their libraries revealed, and may draw cards from the bottom of their library rather than the top.
Whenever a player loses life, they may pay {1}. If they don&apos;t, they shuffle. (Damage causes loss of life.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/184.png" num="28">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Snake Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>May I Have This Dance?</name>
			<text>Each attacking player secretly chooses an attacking creature they control and each player that isn&apos;t attacking secretly chooses a creature they control that isn&apos;t attacking. Each player gains control of the creature chosen by the player to their right. Tap each creature gained control of by an attacking player this way. Those creatures attack the permanent or player that the creature their controller owned was previously attacking. (Any attacking creatures controlled by players that aren&apos;t attacking are no longer attacking.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/185.png" num="44">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Myxomitosis</name>
			<text>Provoke (Whenever this creature attacks, you may have target creature defending player controls untap and block it if able.)
Myriad (Whenever this creature attacks, for each opponent other than defending player, you may create a token that&apos;s a copy of this creature that&apos;s tapped and attacking that player or a planeswalker they control. If one or more tokens are created this way, exile the tokens at end of combat.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/186.png" num="46">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Rabbit Shapeshifter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cornucopia Utopia</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, you get three focus counters. (At the beginning of your draw step, lose a focus counter if you have any. When you do, draw a card.)
If you would draw a card while Cornucopia Utopia is in your graveyard, you may instead pay {2}{U}. If you do, draw two cards.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/187.png" num="74">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>World Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Deathsatyr Neophyte</name>
			<text>(As this Saga enters and after your draw step, add a lore counter. Sacrifice after III.)
Whenever another creature leaves the battlefield on your turn, you may remove a counter from target permanent.
Draw a card, then discard a card.
Mill four cards, then return a card from your graveyard to your hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/188.png" num="76">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>saga</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment Creature — Saga Goat Sorcerer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Introspection</name>
			<text>As an additional cost to cast this spell, reveal your hand.
When Introspection dies, you can&apos;t target yourself for the rest of the game.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/189.png" num="83">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Incarnation</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sewn Shut</name>
			<text>This spell costs {U} (or {1}) less for each ability you don&apos;t control on the stack.
Counter any number of target activated or triggered abilities.
Target creature loses all abilities and gets -2/-0 until end of turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/190.png" num="98">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sonder</name>
			<text>Creatures have myriad.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/191.png" num="100">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Incarnation</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>8/8</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Buried Darlings</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, each player exiles a nonland permanent card from their graveyard. Put each creature card with mana value 3 or less exiled this way onto the battlefield under your control, then this creature gains the non-characteristic defining abilities of each other card exiled this way.
Dredge 3 (If you would draw a card, you may mill three cards instead. If you do, return this card from your graveyard to your hand.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/192.png" num="124">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Reflection</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5B</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Killer&apos;s Tell</name>
			<text>Spree (Choose one or more additional costs.) (Choose one or more additional costs.)
+ {WB} — Destroy target unnatural creature. (A permanent is unnatural if it is merged, has five or more types, or has negative stats.)
+ {UB} — Destroy target creature targeted by a spell or ability you don&apos;t control.
+ {BR} — Destroy target creature you own.
+ {BG} — Destroy target modified creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/193.png" num="143">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>B</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Flushed Capyiary</name>
			<text>Flying, haste
Whenever you expend 4, expend 8, or expend 12, create a Blood token. (It&apos;s an artifact with &quot;{1}, {T}, Discard a card, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.&quot;. You expend N as you spend your Nth total mana to cast spells during a turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/194.png" num="176">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Capybara Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Opening Performance</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it and note which draft round it is.
Whenever a lore counter is put on this Saga, it deals 2 damage to any target.
I — It you noted the first draft round for cards named Opening Performance, you may discard any number of cards, then draw that many cards.
II — It you noted the second draft round for cards named Opening Performance, up to two target creatures can&apos;t block this turn.
III — It you noted any draft round other than the first or second for cards named Opening Performance, remove all counters from this Saga.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/195.png" num="191">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>saga</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Saga</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Roadside Apotheosis</name>
			<text>Cast this spell only before attackers are declared.
Target opponent chooses which creatures attack this turn.
Target opponent chooses which creatures block this turn and how those creatures block.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/196.png" num="197">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Anti-Authorosaurus</name>
			<text>When Anti-Authorosaurus enters, choose one—
• Vandalise it, then vandalise target noncreature permanent. (To vandalise a permanent, put a counter of each kind among permanents you control onto it.)
• Destroy target artifact.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/197.png" num="213">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur Skeleton</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Heir Presumptive</name>
			<text>For each color, the first time a player spends three or more mana of that color while casting a spell this game, they become the monarch.
Whenever you become the monarch, choose one—
• You get a focus counter.
• Proliferate.
• Add {G}{G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/198.png" num="235">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Koiotemyona of the Pond</name>
			<text>{0}: Add {G}. Activate only once each turn and only if this card is the top card of your graveyard.
You may discard this card any time you could cast an instant. (This isn&apos;t an activated ability.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/199.png" num="236">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Beast Avatar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>5G</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fabricated Real</name>
			<text>Other nonland permanents with no counters on them have phasing. (They phase in or out before you untap during each of your untap steps. While phased out, they&apos;re treated as though they don&apos;t exist.)
{2}: Put a stun counter on target permanent you control. Any player may activate this ability. (If a permanent with a stun counter would become untapped, remove one from it instead.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/200.png" num="266">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>World Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>WU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Permutation Regurgitation</name>
			<text>As this Saga enters, note the name of a random Saga card (from all of Magic).
Roll a d10—
[b]1-3[/b] | The player with the lowest life total chooses a chapter ability of the noted Saga. Trigger it.
[b]4-5[/b] | Trigger the noted Saga&apos;s chapter I ability.
[b]6-7[/b] | Trigger the noted Saga&apos;s chapter II ability.
[b]8-9[/b] | Trigger the noted Saga&apos;s chapter III ability.
[b]10[/b] | Choose a chapter ability of the noted Saga.Trigger it.
​
​</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/201.png" num="280">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>saga</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Saga</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3GU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Spilling Happenstance</name>
			<text>Whenever a replacement effect replaces an event, you may have that event happen in addition to the event replacing it. Do this only once each turn. (Whenever something would happen &quot;instead&quot;, you may have both happen. Whenever something would be skipped, you may have it happen anyways.)
{T}: Add one mana of any color. You may instead pay {1}. If you do, add one mana of any color.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/202.png" num="323">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Discerning Hoarder</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
Instead of drafting a card from a booster pack, you may pass that pack without drafting a card from it. If you do, turn this card face down, then you may draft an additional card from the next booster pack passed to you.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/203.png" num="30">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spirit</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Quantity Over Quality</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
You can&apos;t cast creature spells with mana value 4 or greater.
Whenever you cast a creature spell, you may pay {W}. If you do, copy that spell. Do this only once each turn. (A copy of a permanent spell becomes a token.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/204.png" num="52">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Skyclave Line-Slinger</name>
			<text>When this creature attacks, for each opponent, tap up to one target creature that player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/205.png" num="59">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Kor Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Frilled Striker</name>
			<text>Whenever this creature attacks, until end of turn, if you would draw one or more cards, you draw that many cards plus one instead.
Blitz {3}{U} (If you cast this spell for its blitz cost, it gains haste and &quot;When this creature dies, draw a card.&quot; Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/206.png" num="79">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Salamander Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tide Rider</name>
			<text>Gain the next level as a sorcery to add its ability.
Tidal (When this creature enters, if there is no tide, it becomes low tide. This has the text box and size associated with the current tide.)
Low Tide | 3/3
{T}: Scry 1. It becomes Mid Tide.
Mid Tide | 4/4
{T}: Draw a card. It becomes High Tide.
High Tide | 5/5
{T}: Discard your hand, then draw seven cards. It becomes Low Tide.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/207.png" num="107">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Merfolk Sorcerer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3U</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Avatar of Death</name>
			<text>Menace, haste
This creature enters with seven +1/+1 counters on it for each player who has lost the game this game.
Whenever a player loses the game, put seven +1/+1 counters on this creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/208.png" num="117">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Spirit Avatar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>B</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Concentric Return</name>
			<text>Return target creature card from your graveyard to your hand. That card perpetually gains cascade. (When you cast that spell, exile cards from the top of your library until you exile a nonland card that costs less. You may cast it without paying its mana cost. Put the exiled cards on the bottom in a random order.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/209.png" num="125">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Golden-Scale Gorgon</name>
			<text>Encore {4}{B}{B} ({4}{B}{B}, Exile this card from your graveyard: For each opponent, create a token copy that attacks that opponent this turn if able. They gain haste. Sacrifice them at the beginning of the next end step. Activate only as a sorcery.)
Each player sacrifices a creature.
Target creature you control gains deathtouch until end of turn.
You draw a card and lose 1 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/210.png" num="138">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>saga</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment Creature — Saga Gorgon</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2B</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>All is Tinder</name>
			<text>Kicker—{R} and/or discard a card and/or put a card from your hand on the bottom of your library and/or sacrifice an artifact and/or sacrifice a land. (You may pay {R} and/or discard a card and/or put a card from your hand on the bottom of your library and/or sacrifice an artifact and/or sacrifice a land in addition to any other costs as you cast this spell.)
Draw a card for each time this spell was kicked.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/211.png" num="163">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Velocidragster</name>
			<text>Haste
Saddle 1 (Tap any number of other creatures you control with total power 1 or more: This Mount becomes saddled until end of turn. Saddle only as a sorcery.)
Whenever this creature attacks while saddled, it can&apos;t be blocked this turn except by creatures with haste.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/212.png" num="207">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur Mount</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Volcanic Bruiser</name>
			<text>Trample
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to an opponent, it deals that much damage to each other opponent.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/213.png" num="208">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental Berserker</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Audience With Nature</name>
			<text>Parley — Each player reveals the top card of their library. Put each land card revealed this way onto the battlefield tapped under your control. Then each player draws a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/214.png" num="214">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>2GG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Garden Philanthropist</name>
			<text>{T}: Add two mana of any one color. At the beginning of each opponent&apos;s next main phase, that player adds one mana of a color of their choice. Activate only during your turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/215.png" num="232">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Frog Druid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
				<loyalty>2</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tharo, Leyline Puppeteer</name>
			<text>Land creatures you control have myriad. The copies enter untapped.
Lands you control that entered this turn are 3/3 Elemental creatures with haste, vigilance, and trample in addition to their other types.
{1}{G}, {T}: Exile target land you control, then return it to the battlefield under your control. It enters untapped.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/216.png" num="254">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Treefolk Druid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4GG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Aminatou, Many-Fated</name>
			<text>When Aminatou, Many-Fated enters, return another target creature to its owner&apos;s hand. Each player other than that creature&apos;s owner conjures a duplicate of that card into their hand. The duplicates perpetually gain &quot;You may spend mana as though it were mana of any color to cast this spell.&quot;
At the beginning of each player&apos;s upkeep, choose a card name. Whenever a player casts a spell with the chosen name this turn, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/217.png" num="256">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Insanity Amplifier</name>
			<text>When this artifact enters, for each player, put a +1/+1 counter on up to one target creature that player controls.
{B}{G}, {T}: Proliferate. Each opponent loses life equal to the number of counters put on them or permanents they control this way. (To proliferate, choose any number of permanents and/or players, then give each another counter of each kind already there.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/218.png" num="271">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>BG</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>William Shakespeare</name>
			<text>When William Shakespeare enters, put a lore counter on each other nontoken creature.
Each other nontoken creature is a Saga enchantment in addition to its other types and has &quot;I — Scry 1.&quot; and &quot;III — You draw a card and lose 1 life.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/219.png" num="298">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Bard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Yovan, Imposing Challenger</name>
			<text>Whenever Yovan, Imposing Challenger attacks, target creature defending player controls can&apos;t block this turn. Goad it. (Until your next turn, that creature attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.)
Goaded creatures get +3/+3 and have trample.
{3}: Goad Yovan. Only your opponents may activate this ability, and only if it hasn&apos;t been activated since your last upkeep.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/220.png" num="299">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Venture Onward // To Glory</name>
			<text>Create two 1/1 white Soldier creature tokens. (Then exile this card. You may cast the Omen later from exile.)

---

Creatures you control get +2/+0 until end of turn. (Then shuffle this card into its owner&apos;s library.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/221.png" num="306">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>split</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery — Adventure // Instant — Omen</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1W // 2R</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Termination Construct</name>
			<text>Indestructible, trample, haste
When this creature enters, choose an opponent.
This creature attacks each combat if able and attacks the chosen player if able.
When the chosen player loses the game, sacrifice this creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/222.png" num="325">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>6</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<pt>6/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Secluded Beach</name>
			<text>This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {C}.
{2}, {T}: Conjure a card named Buried Treasure onto the battlefield. (It&apos;s a {2} Treasure artifact with &quot;{T}, Sacrifice this artifact: Add one mana of any color.&quot; and &quot;{5}, Exile this artifact from your graveyard: Discover 5. Activate only as a sorcery.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/223.png" num="359">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Forbidden Pact</name>
			<text>Contingency {4} (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. You may turn it face up any time for {4}.)
When you turn this conspiracy face up, if there isn&apos;t an archenemy you may conjure the cards from an Archenemy scheme deck of your choice into your command zone and shuffle it. You gain 20 life and become the archenemy.
Whenever you lose the game, if you&apos;re the archenemy, each opponent wins the game.
Whenever you attack, if you&apos;re the archenemy, set a scheme into motion.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/224.png" num="6">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Second Floor Mage</name>
			<text>Lifelink
Whenever a player gains life for the second time each turn, that player ventures into The Tower. (They enter the next room in the current The Tower dungeon. If there isn&apos;t one, they enter The First Floor.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/225.png" num="53">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Cleric</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Trade Enforcer</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
Immediately after the draft, each player must reveal a card from their draft pool. Starting with you, each player may take one of the revealed cards and add it to their draft pool.
When this creature enters, redistribute up to four life totals. (You choose who gets which life total.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/226.png" num="64">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Noble</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4WW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Become {Un}Lost</name>
			<text>Recleave {2}{U}{U} (You may cast this spell for its recleave cost. If you do, remove the words in square brackets and add the words in curly braces.)
Scry 2, then draw two cards. [Then, shuffle the drawn cards back into your library.]
{Put this card on the bottom of your library.} [(Shuffle this card into your library.)]</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/227.png" num="68">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant — Omen</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>0</manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Third Floor Mage</name>
			<text>Prowess (Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, this creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
Whenever a player draws their second card each turn, that player ventures into The Tower. (They enter the next room in the current The Tower dungeon. If there isn&apos;t one, they enter The First Floor.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/228.png" num="106">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fourth Floor Mage</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
Whenever a creature card is put into a player&apos;s graveyard from anywhere for the second time each turn, that player ventures into The Tower. (They enter the next room in the current The Tower dungeon. If there isn&apos;t one, they enter The First Floor.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/229.png" num="136">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Snake Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fifth Floor Mage</name>
			<text>Menace
Whenever a player casts their second noncreature spell each turn, that player ventures into The Tower. (They enter the next room in the current The Tower dungeon. If there isn&apos;t one, they enter The First Floor.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/230.png" num="175">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Goat Sorcerer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Might of Nature // Sudden Eruptions</name>
			<text>Enchant creature
Enchanted creature gets +1/+1 for each land you control and has melee.

---

Each land you control deals 1 damage to target creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/231.png" num="238">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura // Sorcery — Omen</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG // R</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Renewed Growth // Forest Spread</name>
			<text>Search your library for up to X land cards and put them onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle.

---

Create a tapped Forest token.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/232.png" num="244">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery // Sorcery — Adventure</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>XGG // 1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sixth Floor Mage</name>
			<text>Vigilance
Whenever a creature enters under a player&apos;s control for the second time each turn, that player ventures into The Tower. (They enter the next room in the current The Tower dungeon. If there isn&apos;t one, they enter The First Floor.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/233.png" num="250">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Orc Druid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Combat Instructor</name>
			<text>{Q}{RG}, {Q}{GW}: If {R} was spent to activate this ability, Combat Instructor deals 2 damage to each opponent. If {G} was spent to activate this ability, put a +1/+1 counter on another creature. If {W} was spent to activate this ability, you gain 5 life. Activate only once each turn. ({Q}{RG} can be paid by paying {R}, {G}, or {Q}. You can&apos;t choose {Q} for both.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/234.png" num="262">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Cat Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RGW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WRG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Explore the Omenpaths</name>
			<text>The game becomes a Planechase game in addition to its other types. Starting with you, players take turns drafting, revealing, and removing cards from Explore the Omenpaths&apos;s spellbook until it is empty. Players can not draft multiple Phenomenon cards. The active player planeswalks. Draw a card. (Planechase cards are shuffled into the drafter&apos;s planar deck when drafted.)
Disturb {G}{U}
---
(Back): Wanderer&apos;s Talent</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/235_front.png" num="265a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1GU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Wanderer&apos;s Talent</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Wanderer&apos;s Talent</name>
			<text>Path select (Gain either level as a sorcery to add its ability.)
If a player would roll the planar die, they instead roll it twice, then players vote for a roll to ignore. The roller wins ties.
{2}{U}: Level A
While voting, you may vote an additional time.
{2}{G}: Level B
Whenever you win a vote, explore.
---
(Front): Explore the Omenpaths</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/235_back.png" num="265b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Class</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>UG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Explore the Omenpaths</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hazel, Master Forager</name>
			<text>Whenever you sacrifice one or more Foods or exile three or more cards from your graveyard, you may pay 1 life. If you do, draw a card.
{T}B, {T}G, Forage: Create a 1/1 green Squirrel token. ({T}B can be paid by paying {B} or {T}. You can&apos;t pay {T} for both.) (To forage, exile three cards from your graveyard or sacrifice a Food.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/236.png" num="269">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Squirrel Druid</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lobbied Legislator</name>
			<text>This creature&apos;s activated abilities may each only be activated as a sorcery and only once each turn.
You gain 1 life: You lose 1 life.
Draw a card: Discard a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/237.png" num="275">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dragon Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ral, Controlled Storm</name>
			<text>{4}{R}{R}: Exile Ral, then cast him transformed.
[+1]: Create a 1/1 red and blue Elemental creature token.
[-5]: Draft a card from Ral&apos;s spellbook.
[-12]: You get an emblem with &quot;Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, draw up to five cards and put a loyalty counter on each planeswalker you control.&quot;
---
(Back): Ral, Raging Storm</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/238_front.png" num="286a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Ral</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>1UR</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>3</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Ral, Raging Storm</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ral, Raging Storm</name>
			<text>{4}{U}{R}: Transform Ral and draft a card from his spellbook.
[+2]: Draw two cards, then discard two cards.
[+1]: Add {R}{R}{R}. This mana can&apos;t be spent to cast creature spells.
[-2]: Ral Deals 4 damage distributed as you choose among any number of targets.
---
(Front): Ral, Controlled Storm</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/238_back.png" num="286b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Ral</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>5</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Ral, Controlled Storm</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Season of Destruction</name>
			<text>Choose up to five {J} worth of modes. You may choose the same mode more than once.
{J}{BR} — Each opponent loses 1 life. ({J}{BR} is worth one {J} unless you pay {B} or {R}.)
{J}B{J}R — Create a 2/2 red and black Imp creature token with menace.
{J}B{J}{BR}{J}R — This spell deals 2 damage to each creature your opponents control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/239.png" num="291">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3BR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>BR</colors>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Soulfire Staff // Enflame</name>
			<text>Noncreature permanents you control have lifelink.
{T}, Discard a card: Create a copy of this artifact&apos;s adventure. You may cast the copy.

---

Target permanent you control deals 3 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/240.png" num="293">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact // Instant — Adventure</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>1RW // 1R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fragment Memories</name>
			<text>Target player mills six cards.
Disturb—{1}{U}{B}, Exile X other cards from your graveyard. (You may cast this card from your graveyard transformed for its disturb cost.)
---
(Back): Stolen Secrets</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/241_front.png" num="301a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>U/BU/B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Stolen Secrets</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Stolen Secrets</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters or you gain control of it, target player mills X cards and you draw a card.
Whenever a player deals combat damage to you, they gain control of this enchantment. X is the amount of damage they have dealt to you this turn.
---
(Front): Fragment Memories</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/241_back.png" num="301b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Fragment Memories</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rabbit Ritual</name>
			<text>Create two 1/1 white Rabbit creature tokens.
Disturb—{E}{GW}{E}{GW}{E}{GW}{E}{GW}{E}{GW}{E}{GW}, Put a youth counter on each token you control. (You may pay for {E}{GW} by paying an energy counter, {G}, or {W}. You may cast this card from your graveyard transformed for its disturb cost.)
---
(Back): Fibonacci&apos;s Mating</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/242_front.png" num="304a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>G/WG/W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Fibonacci&apos;s Mating</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Fibonacci&apos;s Mating</name>
			<text>At the beginning of you end step, for each token you control, if it doesn&apos;t have a youth counter, create a token that is a copy of that creature and put a youth counter on the copy. Otherwise, remove a youth counter from it.
---
(Front): Rabbit Ritual</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/242_back.png" num="304b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Rabbit Ritual</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>The Farland Tome</name>
			<text>Companion — Your starting deck contains no land cards. (If this card is your chosen companion, you may put it into your hand from outside the game for {3} as a sorcery.)
{T}, Discard a card, Discard another card if this card isn&apos;t on the battlefield or isn&apos;t your companion: Draft, reveal, and remove a card from The Farland Tome&apos;s spellbook. You may activate this ability while this card is outside the game if it is your companion.
{5}: Remove this card from the game and tap it. You may activate this ability from any public zone.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/243.png" num="313">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Artifact</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Omenpath Wanderer</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
Immediately after the draft, open a booster pack from a draftable Strata community set and reveal the contents. Choose four cards from that pack and add them to Omenpath Wanderer&apos;s spellbook. Repeat this process three times.
Whenever this creature or another artifact you control enters, draft a card from Omenpath Wanderer&apos;s spellbook, then discard a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/244.png" num="318">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Timely Platoon</name>
			<text>This creature has backup 1 as long as it&apos;s not a token. (When this creature enters, put a +1/+1 counter on target creature. If that&apos;s another creature, it gains the following abilities until end of turn.)
Myriad (Whenever this creature attacks, for each opponent other than defending player, you may create a token that&apos;s a copy of this creature that&apos;s tapped and attacking that player or a planeswalker they control. Exile the tokens at end of combat.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/245.png" num="63">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Burglar of the Bourgeois</name>
			<text>Skulk (This creature can&apos;t be blocked by creatures with greater power.)
Ward {1}
Whenever this creature attacks, if defending player has more cards in hand than you, exile the top card of that player&apos;s library. During any turn you attacked with a Rebel or Rogue, you may cast that card and you may spend mana as though it were mana of any type to cast that spell.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/246.png" num="71">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Rebel Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Supernatural Espionage</name>
			<text>Fateseal 1, fateseal 1, fateseal 1. (To fateseal 1, look at the top card of an opponent&apos;s library, then you may put it on the bottom of that player&apos;s library.)
Addendum — If you cast this spell during your main phase, scry 1, then draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/247.png" num="104">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1U</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bloodthirsty Leadbeast</name>
			<text>Bloodthirst 2 (If an opponent was dealt damage this turn, this creature enters with two +1/+1 counters on it.)
Each creature you control with counters on it has afflict X, where X is the number of counters on it. (Whenever this creature becomes blocked, defending player loses X life.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/248.png" num="123">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Beast Horror</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3B</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Creation&apos;s Rage</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, return target creature card from your graveyard to the battlefield with a finality counter on it. (If a creature with a finality counter on it would die, exile it instead.)
Creatures you control with finality counters on them get +2/+2 and have menace and trample.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/249.png" num="127">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lieu&apos;s Interrogation</name>
			<text>Each opponent reveals one or more cards from their hand. For each opponent, choose one of the cards they revealed this way. They discard that card. For each card in their hand not revealed this way, they lose 1 life. You gain life equal to the life lost this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/250.png" num="144">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mr. Endelgauss, Profiteer General</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
Ward—Sacrifice a creature.
Whenever a creature dies, if it wasn&apos;t sacrificed, each player other than that creature&apos;s controller loses 1 life and creates a tapped treasure token.
{1}{B}{B}, {T}: Destroy target creature. You gain life equal to its power.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/251.png" num="145">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Smuggling Techneque</name>
			<text>Demonstrate (When you cast this spell, you may copy it. If you do, choose an opponent to also copy it. Players may choose new targets for their copies.)
You draw X cards and lose X life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/252.png" num="151">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>XBBB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Stalking Hassmaske</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
If a creature an opponent controls would die, instead exile it with a capture counter on it.
{T}, Sacrifice this creature: Choose an exiled creature card an opponent owns with a capture counter on it. You may cast it this turn, and you may spend mana as though it were mana of any color to cast it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/253.png" num="154">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Rogue Mutant</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>BB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Gaimontov&apos;s Pageburners</name>
			<text>Prowess (Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, this creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
Whenever this creature enters or attacks, for each opponent, put a burn counter on target creature that player controls. (Damage isn&apos;t removed from creatures with burn counters on them during cleanup steps.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/254.png" num="177">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Moira von Bael, Supersonic</name>
			<text>Split second (As long as this spell is on the stack, players can&apos;t cast spells or activate abilities that aren&apos;t mana abilities.)
First strike
Blitz {1}{R}{R} (If you cast this spell for its blitz cost, it gains haste and &quot;When this creature dies, draw a card&quot;. Sacrifice it at the beginning of the next end step.)
You may cast this card as though it has flash if you cast it for its blitz cost.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/255.png" num="190">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Aerial Superiority</name>
			<text>Destroy target artifact, enchantment, or creature with flying. Scry 1.
Reload (You may cast this card from your graveyard by removing an unblocked attacker you control from combat in addition to paying its other costs. Then exile this card.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/256.png" num="210">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>BF-Class Sniper Rifle</name>
			<text>Call to arms (When this Equipment enters, you may attach it to target Soldier you control. If you don&apos;t, create a 1/1 white Soldier creature token, then attach this to it.)
Equipped creature gets +3/+2 and has trample, reach, ward {3}, and &quot;Whenever this creature attacks, put a stun counter on it.&quot;
Equip {2}{G}</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/257.png" num="217">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Equipment</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Collective Perseverance</name>
			<text>Escalate {G} (Pay this cost for each mode chosen beyond the first.)
Choose one or more —
• Put a +1/+1 counter on target creature you control.
• Put a shield counter on target creature you control. (If it would be dealt damage or destroyed, remove a shield counter from it instead.)
• Target creature you control fights a different creature an opponent controls. (This avoids hexproof and the like, sorry!)
Overload {2}{G}</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/258.png" num="221">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Conformant Huntsman</name>
			<text>Vigilance, reach
Whenever this creature enters or attacks, destroy target complex permanent an opponent controls. (Permanents with two or more permanent types are complex.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/259.png" num="222">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Spider Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Geisterblitzer Commando</name>
			<text>Vigilance
When this creature dies, manifest dread. (Look at the top two cards of your library, then put one onto the battlefield face down as a 2/2 creature and the other into your graveyard. Turn it face up any time for its mana cost if it&apos;s a creature card.)
Encore {4}{G}{G} ({4}{G}{G}, Exile this card from your graveyard: For each opponent, create a token copy that attacks that opponent this turn if able. They gain haste. Sacrifice them at the beginning of the next end step. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/260.png" num="233">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Trenchrunner Ceratops</name>
			<text>This creature and other Dinosaurs you control can&apos;t be the target of spells or abilities your opponents control. The same is true for Dinosaur spells you control and Dinosaur cards you own that aren&apos;t on the battlefield.
{G}{G}, {T}: Target Dinosaur you control fights target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/261.png" num="255">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Poxia, Pestilent Pin-up</name>
			<text>Vigilance; infect (This creature deals damage to creatures in the form of -1/-1 counters and to players in the form of poison counters.)
Whenever one or more creatures an opponent controls die, if one or more of those creatures&apos; toughnesses was less than 1, that creature&apos;s controller gets a poison counter. Otherwise put a +1/+1 counter on Poxia.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/262.png" num="283">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Human Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2BG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Rise of the Gamma Queen</name>
			<text>As an additional cost to cast this spell, sacrifice a nontoken creature.
Each opponent sacrifices a nontoken creature of their choice. Then surveil 3.
Create The Gamma Queen, a legendary X/X black, green, and blue Avatar artifact creature with vigilance, menace, trample, and reach, where X is the number of creature cards in all graveyards.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/263.png" num="289">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>2BGU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>UBG</colors>
				<coloridentity>UBG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Persist Through Pestilence</name>
			<text>Target creature you control gains deathtouch and indestructible until end of turn. Put a +1/+1 counter on it.
Reload (You may cast this card from your graveyard by removing an unblocked attacker you control from combat in addition to paying its other costs. Then exile this card.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/264.png" num="302">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1B/GB/G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Maladapted Multi-Tool</name>
			<text>As this creature enters, choose a type of counter from among flying, first strike, deathtouch, banding, battle cry, changeling, exalted, extort, fear, flanking, hexproof, horsemanship, infect, ingest, intimidate, lifelink, melee, menace, mentor, myriad, phasing, prowess, provoke, reach, shadow, shield, skulk, wither, trample, vigilance, haste and +1/+1. It enters with that type of counter on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/265.png" num="317">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Codex, the Secret Hand</name>
			<text>Before you shuffle your deck to start the game, you may reveal this card from your deck and exile up to three nonland, nonconspiracy cards you drafted with different mana values that aren&apos;t in your starting deck.
[+2]: Copy a card with mana value 2 or less you exiled with cards named Codex, the Secret Hand. You may cast the copy without paying its mana cost.
[-3]: Copy a card with mana value 3, 4, or 5 you exiled with cards named Codex, the Secret Hand. You may cast the copy without paying its mana cost.
[-7]: Copy a card with mana value 6, 7, or 8 you exiled with cards named Codex, the Secret Hand. You may cast the copy without paying its mana cost.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/266.png" num="3">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Codex</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>6</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Extraplanar Operative</name>
			<text>(Start the game with this conspiracy face up in the command zone.)
At the beginning of your first upkeep, put Extraplanar Operative from the command zone onto the battlefield.
[level +1] Look at the top card of target player&apos;s library.
[level -1] Create a 1/1 colorless Construct creature token with defender.
[level -3] Draw a card. Until end of turn, spells you cast cost {1} less to cast.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/267.png" num="5">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Conspiracy Planeswalker — HAL</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<loyalty>1</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Frontline Vanguard</name>
			<text>Melee (Whenever this creature attacks, it gets +1/+1 until end of turn for each opponent you attacked this combat.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/268.png" num="37">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>String of Arrests</name>
			<text>Demonstrate (When you cast this spell, you may copy it. If you do, choose an opponent to also copy it. Players may choose new targets for their copies. Each copy becomes a token.)
Enchant creature or planeswalker
Enchanted permanent can&apos;t attack or block, and its activated abilities can&apos;t be activated unless they&apos;re mana abilities.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/269.png" num="61">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Clyclonic Elemental</name>
			<text>Flying
When this creature enters, return target creature you don&apos;t control to its owner&apos;s hand.
Overload {6}{U}{U} (You may cast this spell for its overload cost. If you do, change &quot;target&quot; in its text to &quot;each.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/270.png" num="72">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Keeper of the Restricted</name>
			<text>Prowess (Whenever you cast a noncreature spell, this creature gets +1/+1 until end of turn.)
When this creature enters, if you cast it, starting with you, each player chooses a card from the Power Nine that hasn&apos;t been chosen this way and conjures a card of that name into their hand.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/271.png" num="86">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1UU</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Public Hearing</name>
			<text>Each opponent secretly chooses a nonland card type. Then those choices are revealed. Counter all other spells of the chosen types. Each opponent who chose a type that wasn&apos;t countered this way draws a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/272.png" num="94">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dynasty Overseer</name>
			<text>Menace
When this creature enters, an opponent of your choice becomes the monarch.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/273.png" num="133">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Secret Service</name>
			<text>Deathtouch
Whenever this creature deals combat damage to a player, you may gain control of a face up conspiracy, emblem, or vanguard in the command zone that player controls.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/274.png" num="148">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Lizard Rogue</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Blasphemy</name>
			<text>This spell costs {1} less to cast for each creature on the battlefield.
Blasphemy deals 13 damage to target creature.
Overload {12}{R} (You may cast this spell for its overload cost. If you do, change &quot;target&quot; in its text to &quot;each.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/275.png" num="169">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>6R</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Hot Chicken</name>
			<text>Haste
Whenever this creature attacks, put a sauce counter on target creature defending player controls. As long as that creature has a sauce counter on it, it&apos;s goaded. (It attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.)
{2}, {T}, Sacrifice this creature: It deals 3 damage to each goaded creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/276.png" num="184">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Food Bird</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Property is Theft</name>
			<text>Enchant nonland permanent
When this Aura enters, untap enchanted permanent and gain control of it.
As long as enchanted permanent is a creature, it has haste and is goaded. (It attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.)
At the beginning of each player&apos;s upkeep, untap enchanted permanent. That player gains control of it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/277.png" num="195">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ahn-Duroo, Man of the Mists</name>
			<text>When Ahn-Duroo enters, if you cast it, conjure a card named Fog into your hand and three more cards named Fog into your library, then shuffle. (They&apos;re {G} instants with &quot;Prevent all combat damage that would be dealt this turn.&quot;)
Whenever damage that would be dealt to you or a permanent you control is prevented, draw a card. This ability triggers only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/278.png" num="211">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Avatar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Democratized Tyrant</name>
			<text>Reveal this card as you draft it. The player to your right chooses one, you choose another one, then the player to your left chooses a third one.
• This spell can&apos;t be countered.
• Hexproof
• Haste
• Trample
• Vigilance
This card has all abilities chosen as you drafted cards named Democratized Tyrant.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/279.png" num="226">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4GG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Divisible Gel</name>
			<text>This creature enters with six +1/+1 counters on it.
If damage would be dealt to this creature while it has a +1/+1 counter on it, prevent that damage and remove that many +1/+1 counters from it. When one or more counters are removed from this creature this way, create an X/X green Ooze creature token, where X is the number of counters removed this way.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/280.png" num="229">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Ooze</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4G</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/0</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Aquatior, The Seas as One</name>
			<text>Colossal — When Aquatior enters, if you cast it, create The Hand of the West Sea and The Hand of the East Sea.
Haste</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/281.png" num="258">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Merfolk God</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3URW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WUR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUR</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Charming Menagerie</name>
			<text>Choose one. Conjure a card of that name onto the battlefield.
• Spore Frog (A {G} 1/1 Frog creature with &quot;Sacrifice this creature: Prevent all combat damage that would be dealt this turn.&quot;)
• Selfless Savior (A {W} 1/1 white Dog creature with &quot;Sacrifice this creature: Another target creature you control gains indestructible until end of turn.&quot;)
• Dryad Militant (A {GW} 2/1 Dryad Soldier creature with &quot;If an instant or sorcery card would be put into a graveyard from anywhere, exile it instead.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/282.png" num="260">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>GW</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>The Game Has Changed</name>
			<text>Choose a card from the Game Changers list, conjure a card of that name into exile. Put that card into your hand at the beginning of your next upkeep.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/283.png" num="267">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>WB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>WB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sirun, Vizier of the God-Pharaoh</name>
			<text>When Sirun enters, if there isn&apos;t an archenemy, you may conjure the cards of the scheme deck from Archenemy: Nicol Bolas into your command zone and shuffle it. You become the archenemy, then set a scheme into motion. (Even though you are archenemy, each of your opponents will still be opponents to you and to one another. You may wish to encourage infighting among them.)
Whenever an ability of a scheme you control triggers, you may pay {UB}{BR}. If you do, copy that ability. You may choose new targets for the copy.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/284.png" num="292">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Snake Cleric</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2UR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>UR</colors>
				<coloridentity>UBR</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Styla, the Radical Tide</name>
			<text>Nontoken creatures you control have riot. (They enter with your choice of a +1/+1 counter or haste.)
[+1]: Untap each creature you control.
[-2]: Target creature you control gains myriad until end of turn.
[-6]: Each player reveals cards from the top of their library until they reveal a creature card. Put those cards onto the battlefield under your control. Then each player shuffles.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/285.png" num="296">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Styla</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>2RG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Automated Authority</name>
			<text>Prototype {1}{W}{W} — 2/2 (You may cast this spell with different mana cost, color, and size. It keeps its abilities and types.)
Council&apos;s dilemma — When this creature enters, starting with you, each player votes for or engage or arrest. For each engage vote, a creature you control gets +X/+X until end of turn. For each arrest vote, exile a creature with power X or less owned by the voter until this creature leaves the battlefield. X is this creature&apos;s power.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/286.png" num="307">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>7</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ambosht, City&apos;s Foundation</name>
			<text>World Ascend (Each player who controls ten or more permanents has the city&apos;s blessing for the rest of the game.)
For each player with the city&apos;s blessing, each other creature with the greatest power among creatures they control has no abilities and can&apos;t attack or block. Ambosht is all colors among those creatures.
{2}: Ambosht&apos;s controller gains 1 life for each of his colors and draws a card. You lose the city&apos;s blessing until end of turn. Any player may activate this ability. Activate only as a sorcery and only once each turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/287.png" num="23">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Giant Noble Artisan</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUBRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Exchanger Courtiurge</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, you and target opponent each draw a card.
As long as this card is in your graveyard, opponents can&apos;t activate abilities of permanents you own.
Outsource — {W}, Discard this card or put a +1/+0 counter on this creature: Counter target spell that targets a permanent, spell, or ability you control. Its controller gains control of target permanent you own. Activate only if this creature has no counters on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/288.png" num="36">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Dwarf Artisan</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>W</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>0/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Immortalize in Stone</name>
			<text>Demonstrate (When you cast this spell, you may copy it. If you do, choose an opponent to also copy it.)
Enchant creature
Enchanted creature is a Shrine enchantment with indestructible. (It loses all other abilities and types.)
{0}: You skip your next turn. This Aura&apos;s owner sacrifices this Aura and each other Aura they control with the same name as it. Any player may activate this ability.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/289.png" num="40">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Enchantment — Sculpture Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3W</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Indecisive Outfitter // Greet Guests</name>
			<text>At the beginning of your upkeep, choose a card type. Spells of that type cost {1} less to cast until your next turn.
Coax — If an opponent has drawn a card this turn, this creature has protection from the last card type chosen for it.

---

You and target opponent each draw two cards. (Then exile this card. You may cast the creature later from exile.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/290.png" num="41">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>adventure</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Human Noble Artisan // Sorcery — Adventure</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WW // 1W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Stand Against the Tide</name>
			<text>Choose one—
• Creatures controlled by up to two target players each get +1/+2 until end of turn.
• All permanents you control phase out, and until your next turn, your life total can&apos;t change and you gain protection from everything. Exile this card. (Treat them and anything attached to them as though they don&apos;t exist until your next turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/291.png" num="60">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2WW</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Conniving Obfusaur</name>
			<text>Whenever this creature attacks, defending player may draw a card. If they do, this creature can&apos;t be blocked this turn.
Each player who controls the most nonland permanents plays with their hand revealed.
Coax — {UB}: This creature phases out. Activate only if an opponent has drawn a card this turn. (Treat it and anything attached to it as though they don&apos;t exist until its controller&apos;s next turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/292.png" num="73">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosuar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pull Back the Curtain</name>
			<text>For each player, exile target nonland permanent that player controls face down. As long as one or more cards remain exiled this way, whenever a player would draw a card, they may instead reveal one of those cards at random. If it&apos;s a card they own, they put it into their hand. Otherwise, they draw a card. (And the revealed card becomes face down again.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/293.png" num="95">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3U</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Archpriest of Culling</name>
			<text>Sacrifice two creatures: Draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/294.png" num="116">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Ogre Cleric</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1BBB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Succumb to Sacrilege</name>
			<text>When this enchantment enters, target creature gets -3/-3 until end of turn.
Whenever an opponent activates an ability of a permanent that isn&apos;t a mana ability, counter that ability unless its controller pays {1} or pays 2 life.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/295.png" num="155">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Kindred Enchantment — Phyrexian</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Echos of Flameteaching</name>
			<text>Exile a card from the top of your library for each mana spent to cast this spell. Until your next end step, you may play those cards. At the beginning of your next end step, if any of those cards remain exiled, Echos of Flameteaching deals damage to any target equal to 1 plus the number of cards that remain exiled.
Flashback {1}{R}{R}{R} (You may cast this card from your graveyard for its flashback cost. Then exile it.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/296.png" num="174">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>R</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Geothermal Magmasaur</name>
			<text>Enrage — Whenever this creature enters or is dealt damage, target creature gains haste until end of turn. Put a trample counter and a spring counter on it. (A creature with spring counters has &quot;{T}: For each spring counter on this creature, add one mana of any color it is or could produce.&quot;)
At the end of each combat on your turn, if you didn&apos;t attack with a modified creature this combat, sacrifice a permanent with a spring counter on it. (Equipment, Auras you control, and counters are modifications.)
{1}{GW}: Untap all attacking creatures.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/297.png" num="180">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental Dinosuar</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>WRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>6/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Plagarist&apos;s Seal</name>
			<text>When this Equipment enters, attach it to target creature.
Equipped creature gets +2/+0 and has &quot;Whenever this creature deals damage to a player, retrofit that many cards from the top of their library. During any turn a player not retrofitted for those cards attacked with a creature, that player may play cards exiled this way, and may spend mana of any type to do so.&quot; (To Retrofit, exile those cards and note those cards for that player).
Equip {2}</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/298.png" num="194">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact — Equipment</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Warwise Retrofitter</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, for each opponent, retrofit the top card of your library (Exile that card and note that card for that player).
Whenever you attack an opponent, you may play a card you retrofitted for them. If you do, exile the top card of your library. That player may play that card as long as it remains exiled, and mana of any type can be spent to do so. Creatures you play this way enter tapped and attacking.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/299.png" num="209">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Viashino Assembly-Worker</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1R</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Loamplate Ankylosaurus</name>
			<text>This creature can block an additional creature each combat.
Enrage — Whenever this creature is dealt damage, untap it. Until your next turn, it has &quot;{T}, Target creature gains absorb 5 until end of turn.&quot; (If a source would deal damage to a creature with absorb 5, prevent 5 of that damage.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/300.png" num="237">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ooze with Potential</name>
			<text>Idealize (When you cast this, you may have target player with the highest life total gain control of it. Targets remain the same.)
Target creature gains trample and gets +1/+1 for each creature you control until end of turn. Blight 1. (Put a -1/-1 counter on a creature you control.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/301.png" num="240">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1G</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Pako, Playful Mosspup</name>
			<text>Haste
Parley — Whenever Pako attacks, each player reveals the top card of their library. Put a +1/+1 counter on Pako for each noncreature, nonland card revealed this way. Then each player draws a card.
As long as you control a blue legendary creature, each player plays with the top card of their library revealed, and you may play creature cards from the top of players&apos; libraries and may spend mana as though it were of any type to do so.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/302.png" num="241">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Elemental Dog</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3G</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Territorial Dispute</name>
			<text>Target creature you control fights target creature you don&apos;t control. When a creature dealt damage this way dies this turn, you may have its controller put a land card from their hand onto the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/303.png" num="253">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>G</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dawngale, the Crimson Sky</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance, trample
Whenever Dawngale deals combat damage to a player, target player draws two cards and creates a red Ragestone artifact token with &quot;Whenever you attack with one or more creatures, this token deals 2 damage to you.&quot;
Outsource — {G}, Discard Dawngale or put a +1/+0 counter on this artifact: Destroy target artifact or enchantment. Its controller gains control of target permanent you own. Activate only if Dawngale has no counters on it.
Crew 3</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/304.png" num="263">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Artifact — Vehicle</type>
				<maintype>Artifact</maintype>
				<manacost>BRG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>BRG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/6</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Kalmos Valorseeker</name>
			<text>The &quot;legend rule&quot; doesn&apos;t apply to Rhinos you control.
Sacrifice a nontoken creature with mana value 4 or less: Search your library for a creature, enchantment, or instant card with mana value 4 or less and with a different mana value from the sacrificed creature or any non-Rhino permanent you control, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/305.png" num="272">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Creature — Rhino Warrior</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1WUB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WUB</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUB</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Bosko, Surprise Contestant</name>
			<text>Creature tokens are goaded. (They attack each combat if able and attack a player other than you if able.)
[+2]: Create a 3/1 red Viking Chef creature token and a Food token. They gain haste. (The Food doesn&apos;t care.)
[-9]: Target player gets an emblem with &quot;Creature spells you cast cost {X} less and artifact and enchantment spells your opponents cast cost {X} more to cast where X is the number of tokens on the battlefield.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/306.png" num="300">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>3R/GG</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>5</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Prestidigitation</name>
			<text>Choose one—
• Sensory Effect — Put at stun counter on target creature.
• Clean or Soil — Return target artifact or enchantment to its owner&apos;s hand.
• Light Play — Tap or untap target permanent.
• Minor Sensation — Scry 3.
• Magic Mark — Target permanent becomes the color of your choice until end of turn.
• Minor Creation — Create a Clue token. (It&apos;s a colorless artifact token with &quot;{2}, Sacrifice this artifact: Draw a card.&quot;)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/307.png" num="303">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>W/U</manacost>
				<cmc>1</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sovereign&apos;s Stratagem</name>
			<text>Master plan (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose an opponent and a card name. You may turn this conspiracy face up any time and reveal those names for {X}, where X is that card&apos;s mana value.)
Whenever a creature with the chosen name dies to combat damage while attacking the chosen player, you win the game.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/308.png" num="19">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost>X</manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>ASCII C4tz</name>
			<text>Lifelink
Encore {2}{W}{W}</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/309.png" num="25">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ghost Shield</name>
			<text>Enchant creature
Umbra armor (If enchanted creature would be destroyed, instead remove all damage from it and destroy this Aura.)
Enchanted creature has vigilance and hexproof from defending players.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/310.png" num="38">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Psychic Angel</name>
			<text>Flying
Whenever this creature attacks, venture into Kalpan. (If you don&apos;t have one there already, conjure a copy of Psychesculptor Kalpan into the command zone and venture into him. Otherwise, advance to the next room.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/311.png" num="51">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Angel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2W</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Keeper of the Abecedaria</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, choose a language this creature knows, then conjure a number cards at random from the corresponding abecedary into your library equal to your devotion to blue, then shuffle. Those cards perpetually gain &quot;You may spend blue mana as though it were mana of any type to pay this card&apos;s nonblue mana costs.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/312.png" num="85">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Surrakar Advisor</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>UUUU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mbe Pag-ong, Lord of the Deep</name>
			<text>Undaunted, undaunted (This spell costs {2} less to cast for each opponent.)
Secret council—Whenever Mbe Pag-ong, Lord of the Deep attacks, each player secretly votes for shock or awe, then those votes are revealed. For each shock vote, tap target creature. For each awe vote, draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/313.png" num="89">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Enchantment Creature — Elder Elemental Turtle</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>8UU</manacost>
				<cmc>10</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/5</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Warping Lance</name>
			<text>Choose one—
• Warp target creature. (Exile it. Its owner may cast it from exile on a later turn.)
• Target creature&apos;s owner puts it on the top or bottom of their library.
Draw a card.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/314.png" num="110">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>UU</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Wave of Whimsy</name>
			<text>Choose two—
• Generate three random fast effects, then put one of them on the stack.
• Counter target spell.
• Draw a card.
• Muse 1.
Rebound (If you cast this spell from your hand, exile it as it resolves. At the beginning of your next upkeep, you may cast this card from exile without paying its mana cost.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/315.png" num="111">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Grave Wanderer</name>
			<text>Flash
Cast this spell only if a creature died this turn.
Afterlife 1 (Whenever this creature dies, create a 1/1 white and black Spirit creature token with flying.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/316.png" num="139">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Skeleton Warlock</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1B</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>5/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Umbral Strength</name>
			<text>Enchant creature
Umbra armor (If enchanted creature would be destroyed, instead remove all damage from it and destroy this Aura.)
Enchanted creature gets +1/+1.
At the beginning of your upkeep, if this card is in your graveyard with three or more cards above it, you may return it to the battlefield.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/317.png" num="160">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment — Aura</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>BB</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ætherslinger</name>
			<text>Assist (Another player can pay up to {X}{2} of this spell&apos;s cost. You choose the value of X.)
When you cast this spell, the player that assisted you draws a card if they spent more mana to cast it than you did.
When this creature enters, you get X {E} (energy counters).
{R}, {E}, {T}: This creature deals 2 damage to any target.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/318.png" num="162">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Ætherborn Artificer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>X2R</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Arcane Attendant</name>
			<text>When this creature enters, if you&apos;re the monarch, return target instant or sorcery card from your graveyard to your hand. Otherwise, you become the monarch.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/319.png" num="166">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Merfolk Wizard</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>RR</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Iaridh&apos;s Vengeance</name>
			<text>This spell deals 2 damage to each opponent and each creature they control.
Potential {WB}{WB}— If {WB}{WB} was spent to cast this spell, you gain life equal to the excess damage dealt this way. (This card&apos;s potential was realized if {W}{W}, {W}{B}, or {B}{B} was spent to cast it.)
Fateful hour—If you have 5 or less life, this spell has deathtouch.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/320.png" num="185">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>3RR</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>WBR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Thunderous Charge</name>
			<text>Creatures you control get +2/+1 until end of turn.
Addendum—If you cast this spell during your main phase, creatures without flying can&apos;t block a creature alone this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/321.png" num="206">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>2RR</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Farseeker</name>
			<text>Reach
When this creature enters, you may have it fight another target creature. When you do, if both creatures survive, the controller of each creature draws a card and you may play an additional land this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/322.png" num="231">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elf Archer</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Say Goodbye to Spring</name>
			<text>Synthetic (This is an artifact except while resolving or on the battlefield.)
Reveal this card as you draft it and note how many cards you&apos;ve drafted this draft round, including this card.
Put a number of +1/+1 counters on target creature equal to the highest number you noted for cards named Say Goodbye to Spring.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/323.png" num="247">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery — Single</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>1GG</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Search for Overmorrow</name>
			<text>Demonstrate (When you cast this spell, you may copy it. If you do, choose an opponent to also copy it.)
Search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle.
Suspend 2—{G}{G} (Rather than cast this card from your hand, you may pay {G}{G} and exile it with two time counters on it. At the beginning of your upkeep, remove a time counter. When the last is removed, you may cast it without paying its mana cost.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/324.png" num="248">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>2GG</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Now We Know Our ABCs!</name>
			<text>Parley— Each player reveals the top card of their library. For each nonland card revealed this way, conjure a copy of that card into your hand except the copy has &quot;You may spend mana as though it were mana of any type to cast this spell.&quot; Then each player draws a card.
If the names of the revealed cards include all twenty-six letters of the English alphabet, you win the game.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/325.png" num="279">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Sorcery</type>
				<maintype>Sorcery</maintype>
				<manacost>2GGWW</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>WG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Stoic Angel</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance
Players can&apos;t untap more than one creature during their untap steps.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/326.png" num="294">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Angel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1GWU</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>WUG</colors>
				<coloridentity>WUG</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Lore Seeker</name>
			<text>Reveal booster pack as you draft it. After you draft this card, you may add a booster pack to the draft. (Your next pick is from that booster pack. Pass it to the next player and it&apos;s drafted this draft round.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/327.png" num="315">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Artifact Creature — Construct</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Arboreal Nymph</name>
			<text>({T}: Add {G}. This permanent is affected by summoning sickness.)
Tempting offer—When this creature enters, if it isn&apos;t a token, create a token copy of it, then each opponent may create a token copy of it. For each opponent who does, you create a token copy of this creature. If each opponent created a token, each token created this way gains haste.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/328.png" num="328">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Land Creature — Forest Dryad</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Allegiant Oath</name>
			<text>Hidden agenda (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose a card name. You may turn this conspiracy face up any time and reveal that name.)
Each planeswalker you control with the chosen name enters with two additional loyalty counters on it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/329.png" num="1">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Second Act</name>
			<text>Hidden agenda (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose a card name. You may turn this conspiracy face up any time and reveal that name.)
Creature cards with the chosen name in your graveyard have encore. The encore cost is equal to its mana cost. (Pay that cost and exile that card from your graveyard: For each opponent, create a token copy that attacks that opponent this turn if able. They gain haste. Sacrifice them at the beginning of the next end step. Activate only as a sorcery.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/330.png" num="15">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<loyalty>0</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Angel of Reprisal</name>
			<text>Flying, vigilance
Whenever a creature deals damage to you, it deals that much damage to itself.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/331.png" num="24">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Angel</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3WW</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
				<loyalty>2</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Don&apos;t Let it End</name>
			<text>Contingency {3}{W} (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. You may turn it face up at any time by paying {3}{W}.) (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. You may turn it face up any time for {3}{W}.)
When this conspiracy is turned face up, the next time target player would lose the game this turn, instead that player&apos;s life total becomes 1, and if that player is an opponent, you and that opponent each draw two cards.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/332.png" num="32">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy — Agenda</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Out to Pasture</name>
			<text>Skill (When you cast a permanent spell with a loyalty ability, you may exile this card from your graveyard to add it to that spell as an additional loyalty ability.)
[level -1] Exile target creature with power 2 or less. Its controller creates a Food token.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/333.png" num="50">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>leveler</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>1W</manacost>
				<cmc>2</cmc>
				<colors>W</colors>
				<coloridentity>W</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Cunning Courtier</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
As you draft a creature card, you may remove it from the draft face up.
You may cast this card as a copy of any card removed from the draft with a card named Cunning Courtier. (You pay the costs of the removed card instead of this card&apos;s costs.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/334.png" num="75">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Shapeshifter</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2U</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Isila, Portal Mage</name>
			<text>[+1]: The next time one or more creatures attack you or Isila before your next turn, you may redirect which player or planeswalker one of those creatures is attacking.
[-3]: Another target creature or planeswalker&apos;s controller puts it on the top or bottom of their library.
[-6]: Choose a creature, planeswalker, emblem, or conspiracy. Gain control of it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/335.png" num="84">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Isila</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>3UU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>U</colors>
				<coloridentity>U</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Exilius, Void Thrall</name>
			<text>Draft this card face up.
As you draft a card, you may remove it from the draft face down. (Those cards aren&apos;t in your card pool.)
This planeswalker enters with a loyalty counter on it for each card removed from the draft with cards named Exilius, Void Thrall.
[-1]: Each opponent discards a card.
[-3]: Each opponent sacrifices a nontoken creature.
[-6]: Each opponent gets an emblem with &quot;Whenever you draw a card, you lose 1 life.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/336.png" num="134">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Exilius</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>3BB</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>0</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Shorthand Initiate</name>
			<text>/TKEGT /TUFP
/AT /-T /TKPWEUBPG /OF /KWRUR /UP /KAOEP /W-B /KWRU /TKRAU /AEU /KARD /SKW- /KWRU /HROS 1 /HRAOEUF /R-R</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/337.png" num="150">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>/KRAOE /KHUR — /HU /PHAPB /AD /SRAOEUS /-R</type>
				<maintype>/KHUR</maintype>
				<manacost>1BB</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Goblin Bomb Squad</name>
			<text>Flash
Storm (When you cast this spell, copy it for each spell cast before it this turn. You may choose new targets for the copies. Copies become tokens.)
{R}, Sacrifice this creature: It deals 4 damage to each creature that&apos;s blocking it.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/338.png" num="181">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Goblin Soldier</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>3R</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<pt>1/1</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>The Hellhound</name>
			<text>Whenever a creature an opponent controls enters from a graveyard, if this card is in your graveyard, return this card to your hand and put a finality counter on that creature.
[-2]: Discard your hand, then draw two cards.
[-4]: The Hellhound deals 5 damage to each creature.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/339.png" num="183">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Hellhound</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>4RR</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>R</colors>
				<coloridentity>R</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>6</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Dark-Matter Chromasaur</name>
			<text>Myriad (Whenever this creature attacks, for each opponent other than defending player, you may create a token that&apos;s a copy of this creature that&apos;s tapped and attacking that player or a planeswalker they control. Exile the tokens at end of combat.)
Vivoid — This creature gets +1/+1 for each color among permanents you control as long as a nonland permanent left the battlefield this turn or a spell was warped this turn.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/340.png" num="224">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Dinosaur</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>2G</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<pt>3/3</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Personal Retreat</name>
			<text>Hidden agenda (Start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone and secretly choose a card name. You may turn this conspiracy face up any time and reveal that name.)
Discard a Forest card: Search your library for a nonbasic land card with the chosen name, reveal it, put it into your hand, then shuffle.
Nonbasic lands you control with the chosen name have &quot;{T}: Add {G}.&quot;</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/341.png" num="242">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>X</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Sidra, the Python</name>
			<text>Whenever you activate an ability of a Sidra planeswalker you control, create a 1/1 green Snake creature token with &quot;When this creature dies, you may put a creature or planeswalker card from your hand onto the battlefield.&quot;
[+2]: Surveil 1. (Look at the top card of your library. You may put it into your graveyard.)
[-2]: Target creature you control fights target creature you don&apos;t control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/342.png" num="249">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Sidra</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>4GG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>G</colors>
				<coloridentity>G</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Leyline of Lost Memories</name>
			<text>If this card is in your opening hand, you may begin the game with it on the battlefield.
Whenever you cast a spell, each opponent mills a number of cards equal to that spell&apos;s mana value.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/343.png" num="274">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Enchantment</type>
				<maintype>Enchantment</maintype>
				<manacost>2UB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>UB</colors>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Mesmoth</name>
			<text>Flying
When this creature enters, goad each creature you don&apos;t control. (Until your next turn, that creature attacks each combat if able and attacks a player other than you if able.)
Whenever a goaded creature dies, create a 1/1 green Insect creature token.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/344.png" num="276">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Insect Horror</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4RG</manacost>
				<cmc>6</cmc>
				<colors>RG</colors>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
				<pt>4/4</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Nebula Lion</name>
			<text>Flash
When this creature enters, up to one target creature gains double strike until end of turn. You may attach up to one Equipment you control to it.
Warp {1}{RW} (You may cast this card from your hand for its warp cost. Exile this creature at the beginning of the next end step, then you may cast it from exile on a later turn.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/345.png" num="278">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Cat</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>1RW</manacost>
				<cmc>3</cmc>
				<colors>WR</colors>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
				<pt>2/2</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Quick Visit</name>
			<text>Search your library for a planeswalker card, put it onto the battlefield, and activate one of its loyalty abilities. Then shuffle it into your library. (You still must pay the loyalty cost for the ability).</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/346.png" num="284">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Instant</type>
				<maintype>Instant</maintype>
				<manacost>3WU</manacost>
				<cmc>5</cmc>
				<colors>WU</colors>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>3</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Tumult</name>
			<text>Trample
Ward—Sacrifice two lands.
Landfall — Whenever a land you control enters, unearth up to one target creature or planeswalker card. (To unearth a card, return it from your graveyard to the battlefield. It gains haste. Exile it at the beginning of the next end step or if it would leave the battlefield.)</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/347.png" num="297">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Creature — Elemental Incarnation</type>
				<maintype>Creature</maintype>
				<manacost>4BRG</manacost>
				<cmc>7</cmc>
				<colors>BRG</colors>
				<coloridentity>BRG</coloridentity>
				<pt>7/7</pt>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>2</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Cabin</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both green and white, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {G} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/348.png" num="347">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Coast</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both blue and red, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {U} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/349.png" num="348">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Crevasse</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both blue and black, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {U} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/350.png" num="349">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Fortress</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both red and white, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {R} or {W}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/351.png" num="350">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Glacier</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both white and blue, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {W} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/352.png" num="351">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WU</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Mausoleum</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both black and green, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {B} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/353.png" num="352">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Monument</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both green and blue, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {G} or {U}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/354.png" num="353">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>UG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Ridge</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both red and green, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {R} or {G}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/355.png" num="354">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>RG</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Ruins</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both white and black, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {W} or {B}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/356.png" num="355">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>WB</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Remote Volcano</name>
			<text>Hidden sanctuary (You may start the game with this conspiracy face down in the command zone. Whenever a player casts a spell that&apos;s both black and red, you may turn this card face up, then put it into your hand.)
This land enters tapped.
{T}: Add {B} or {R}.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/357.png" num="356">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
				<coloridentity>BR</coloridentity>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Coutier&apos;s Gambit</name>
			<text>Before mulligans, each player puts the top card of their library into the Ante Zone. (Do this after setting starting life totals. The winner of the game gains ownership of the anted cards. This isn&apos;t gambling because it&apos;s a cube.)
If you aren&apos;t playing at least three games after this draft, perpetually transform this card.
---
(Back): Urza&apos;s Grand Design</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/358_front.png" num="4a">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Conspiracy</type>
				<maintype>Conspiracy</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Urza&apos;s Grand Design</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Urza&apos;s Grand Design</name>
			<text>You may play this card from the command zone.
{T}: Add {C}.
Exhaust — Command — {C}: Add {C}{C}. (You may activate this once each from the battlefield and from the command zone.)
---
(Front): Coutier&apos;s Gambit</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/358_back.png" num="4b">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>transform</layout>
				<side>back</side>
				<type>Conspiracy Land — Urza&apos;s</type>
				<maintype>Land</maintype>
				<manacost></manacost>
				<cmc>0</cmc>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>0</tablerow>
			<related attach="transform">Coutier&apos;s Gambit</related>
		</card>
		<card>
			<name>Ana Iora</name>
			<text>[+1]: Each opponent may discard a card. Create a 2/2 black Zombie creature token for each opponent who didn&apos;t discard a card this way.
[-3]: Each opponent sacrifices a nontoken creature.
[-6]: Each player chooses a creature card in their graveyard. Put those cards onto the battlefield under your control.</text>
			<set rarity="rare" picurl="https://strataboocube.github.io/sets/BOO3-files/img/359.png" num="115">BOO3</set>
			<prop>
				<layout>normal</layout>
				<side>front</side>
				<type>Legendary Planeswalker — Liliana</type>
				<maintype>Planeswalker</maintype>
				<manacost>2BB</manacost>
				<cmc>4</cmc>
				<colors>B</colors>
				<coloridentity>B</coloridentity>
				<loyalty>4</loyalty>
			</prop>
			<tablerow>1</tablerow>
		</card>
	</cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>